<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Road Trip USA on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/Road-Trip-USA/</link><description>Recent content in Road Trip USA on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 12:19:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/Road-Trip-USA/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stats &amp; Costs</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/stats-costs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2011 12:19:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/stats-costs/</guid><description>&lt;h3>&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;">Stats:&lt;/span>&lt;/h3>
Duration: &lt;strong>21/22&lt;/strong> days
States Visited:&lt;strong> 4&lt;/strong> (California, Nevada, Arizona, Utah)
&lt;p>Average MPG: &lt;strong>35&lt;/strong>mpg (Ford Focus SES)
Cheapest Gas: &lt;strong>3.449&lt;/strong> (Flagstaff, AZ)
Priciest Gas: &lt;strong>4.199&lt;/strong> (Sunset Blvd, Los Angeles, CA)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Distance Travelled: &lt;strong>3050&lt;/strong> miles
Longest Drive: &lt;strong>372.5&lt;/strong> miles (San Diego&amp;gt; Joshua Tree&amp;gt; Laughlin)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Highest Temp: &lt;strong>116 F&lt;/strong> (Death Valley, CA)
Lowest Temp: &lt;strong>48 F&lt;/strong> (Glacier Point, Yosemite NP, CA)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Highest Altitude: &lt;strong>9945ft&lt;/strong> (Tioga Pass, CA)
Lowest Altitude: &lt;strong>282ft&lt;/strong> below sea level (Badwater Basin, CA)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Cheapest Hotel: &lt;strong>$24.63&lt;/strong> (Golden Nugget, Laughlin, NV)
Priciest Hotel: &lt;strong>$87.48&lt;/strong> (Travelodge LAX, Los Angeles, CA)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Number of Airports: &lt;strong>5&lt;/strong> (LHR, JFK, LAX, DTW, ORD)
Number of problems with Delta: &lt;strong>3&lt;/strong> (Flight Delayed, Lost Baggage, Flight Cancelled)&lt;/p>
&lt;hr />
&lt;h3>&lt;span style="text-decoration: underline;">Costs:&lt;/span>&lt;/h3>
Flights: £1044.26
Accom.: £305.29
Car: £624
Gas: £200
Insurance: £34.95
Spending (inc. food): £652 cash, £1210 fairfx, £202 credit card
TOTAL = &lt;strong>£4273&lt;/strong> approx.
&lt;p>&lt;span style="font-size: 10px;">(rate approx. $1 = £0.60)&lt;/span>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Road Trip USA</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/road-trip-usa/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 18:12:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/road-trip-usa/</guid><description>&lt;p>Our road trip around the West of the USA is now unfortunately over. For all of our blog posts whilst we were on the road &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/tag/road-trip-usa/">read on over here&lt;/a>! See below for the route that we took and our itinerary.&lt;/p>
&lt;iframe width="488" height="350" frameborder="0" scrolling="no" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0" src="https://maps.google.co.uk/maps/ms?msa=0&amp;amp;msid=211455404408841627610.00049104c062ac20b3f4e&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;source=embed&amp;amp;dg=feature&amp;amp;ll=35.603719,-116.630859&amp;amp;spn=12.493453,21.445313&amp;amp;z=5&amp;amp;output=embed">&lt;/iframe>&lt;br />&lt;small>View &lt;a href="https://maps.google.co.uk/maps/ms?msa=0&amp;amp;msid=211455404408841627610.00049104c062ac20b3f4e&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;t=m&amp;amp;source=embed&amp;amp;dg=feature&amp;amp;ll=35.603719,-116.630859&amp;amp;spn=12.493453,21.445313&amp;amp;z=5" style="color:#0000FF;text-align:left">Our Route&lt;/a> in a larger map&lt;/small>
&lt;table>
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;th>Date&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Where&lt;/th>
&lt;th>Sleep&lt;/th>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">25th June&lt;/td>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">Fly from Heathrow &amp;gt; JFK &amp;gt; LAX&lt;/td>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">Travelodge LAX&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>26th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Los Angeles &amp;gt; San Diego&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Motel 6 D/Town&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>27th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Diego&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Motel 6 D/Town&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>28th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Diego &amp;gt; Joshua Tree &amp;gt; Laughlin&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Golden Nugget&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>29th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Laughlin &amp;gt; Route 66 &amp;gt; Flagstaff&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Budget Host Inn Motel*&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>30th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Flagstaff &amp;gt; Grand Canyon&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Mather Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>1st July&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Grand Canyon&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Mather Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>2nd&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Grand Canyon &amp;gt; Monument Valley &amp;gt; Page&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Motel 6*&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>3rd&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Page &amp;gt; Bryce Canyon&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Sunset Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>4th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Bryce Canyon &amp;gt; Zion&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Watchman Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>5th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Zion &amp;gt; Las Vegas&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Bill’s Gamblin’ Hall&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>6th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Las Vegas&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Bill's Gamblin' Hall&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>7th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Las Vegas &amp;gt; Death Valley &amp;gt; Bishop&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Town House Motel*&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>8th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Bishop &amp;gt; Yosemite&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Upper Pines Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">9th&lt;/td>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">Yosemite&lt;/td>
&lt;td style="text-align: left;">Upper Pines Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>10th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Yosemite &amp;gt; San Francisco&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Remo Hotel&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>11th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Francisco&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Remo Hotel&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>12th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>San Francisco &amp;gt; Big Sur&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Kirk Creek Campground&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>13th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Big Sur &amp;gt; Los Angeles&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Orbit Hotel&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>14th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Los Angeles&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Orbit Hotel&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>15th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Los Angeles&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Orbit Hotel&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>16th&lt;/td>
&lt;td>Fly from LAX&amp;gt;Detroit&amp;gt;Chicago&amp;gt;Heathrow&lt;/td>
&lt;td>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;p style="text-align: right;">&lt;em>*Not Prebooked&lt;/em>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Leaving the US</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/leaving-the-us/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2011 12:18:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/leaving-the-us/</guid><description>&lt;p>The alarm went off at 6.30am, but we didn&amp;rsquo;t leave till about 8 as we were packing up and having a browse on the internet. Thought the traffic would be bad (carmageddon) but it was surprisingly quiet the whole way. We stopped off for a McDonalds breakfast which was yummy and included pancakes with maple syrup. We were due to drop off the car to Alamo at 10am, but before that we had to get rid of all our camping gear as we couldn&amp;rsquo;t fit any of it to bring back with us. This was a lot harder than we thought, as we drove around searching for a bin (we tried to find a charity shop but had no luck). We noticed a truck pulling off the road and pulled up next to a dumpster, so we drove around a bit until he was gone and did the same. Was quite funny how we were trying to do it secretly as we weren&amp;rsquo;t sure whether it was legal or not. We continued to Alamo where we quickly and easily dropped the car off with no hassle.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Ieusfp1cNmT6LHWho42ukA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-tJEeio3bGt8/TiQYpKNRWGI/AAAAAAAAAb4/6bE07JV0yes/s400/IMGP1993.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
Was sad to say goodbye, and realised as we'd left on the shuttle bus that we'd left our large iced tea on the back of the trunk (see pic).
&lt;p>Arrived at LAX and headed to the Delta terminal, quick easy check in and straight through security (through the body scanner machines). It is currently being re-done so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a very nice place to wait as there wasn&amp;rsquo;t really anything there. We found an escalator that went down to these tunnels that link the terminals. A nice Southern woman pulled up on a buggy and asked us if we wanted a lift, which we said yes to as we had no idea where we were going. She zoomed along and we were in a much nicer terminal. We went to a few shops and had some food here before heading back and finding some seats to have a read. After a while I decided to look at the time and noticed it was only 20 mins to departure! So we quickly went to the gate and they were shouting &amp;rsquo;last call&amp;rsquo; and so we managed to make it - the last people on the plane oops.. The journey was fine to Detroit and before we knew it we were there. Got a bit lost as we weren&amp;rsquo;t sure whether to pick up our bags (apparently not), and looked around the shops although most were closed. We sat right by the departure gate this time as we didn&amp;rsquo;t wanna miss it. At about 30mins to departure people started to queue so we got up and then noticed on the screen it said Detroit - London Heathrow cancelled, and heard lots of people complaining.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/F6VjzNEz7qnh3wnpyUKlQw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-UY_Lx9IMk9E/TiQYpXWOqtI/AAAAAAAAAZk/arAMUJ_I1Bg/s400/IMGP1994.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
After about 10mins they announced it on the speakers that it was cancelled due to maintenance and they'd give us vouchers for food and a hotel, but there wasn't any space on the direct flight to Heathrow tomorrow. So we waited for ages to get to the front, and we were told we'd be put on flights tomorrow late afternoon to Chicago, then on to Heathrow arriving early morning on Monday. We also had to go back and get a refund on our duty free stuff.
&lt;p>The queue for the hotel shuttles were huuge. Chatted to a guy who had managed to get a direct flight tomorrow somehow who was staying at a different hotel. We were put in to the Metropolitan Hotel which was nice on the outside, but outdated once you get past the lobby. We were really hungry as we hadn&amp;rsquo;t eaten since breakfast and it was around 11.30pm. We asked the guy at the desk how we could use our vouchers and luckily there was a takeaway nearby that accepted them. Tried to call up but was engaged, so had to go online and order it there. Didn&amp;rsquo;t really know how to let them know we were using vouchers so wrote it anywhere we could, mistakenly put it in the part where you ask for special requests on your pizza&amp;hellip; It arrived at 1am and paid with our $12 voucher and pennies for the tax. We then headed to bed, and was woken up at around 2.30am telling us our pizza had arrived even though we ate it an hour earlier.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In the morning we got the shuttle to the airport, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t use the check-in kiosks so had to join the big queue of everyone who was in the same situation as us. Spoke to someone who had been put on a flight to Atlanta and then to Heathrow, seems we were all going different ways. Finally got to the desk where we stood for half an hour as they hadn&amp;rsquo;t actually issued us tickets despite booking us on to the flights. The airport was nice, big and looked quite new. Got on this plane fine, although we didn&amp;rsquo;t have seats together. Unfortunately it was a really small plane and Jon so happened to be sitting by the biggest man imaginable. He was actually sat in Jon&amp;rsquo;s aisle seat with the armrest up, so Jon was stuck by the window with only half a seat&amp;hellip; not pleasant. Luckily the flight was only just over an hour long. We only had an hour to connect and the lady at the Delta desk in Detroit said that it&amp;rsquo;d be fine as the British Airways desks are in the same terminal and we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have to go through security again. Well it turned out that after asking a policeman it was in a different terminal and we&amp;rsquo;d have to redo security. We had to speed walk through and onto the train and check-in all over again. The woman at check-in let us and another family in the same situation go to the front as there wasn&amp;rsquo;t much time left. We managed to stop at duty free with just over 20mins till departure. This plane was a double decker -  the biggest one I&amp;rsquo;ve ever been on and had so much room. Watched some movies including No Strings Attached, and had chicken curry. It was an overnight flight but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t sleep, and there was turbulence most of the way. Finally arrived in the UK at 7am where my Mum was waiting to pick us up and drive us back to Cardiff. Felt weird being back and driving on the other side of the road, and we could already feel the holiday blues kicking in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So our holiday is now over and is going to take some time to sink in, as we have seen and done so much over the past 3 weeks. Will post a stats/favourites page up soon. We had such an amazing time and would definitely recommend a road trip to anyone! :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 21 - Universal studios</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-21-universal-studios/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2011 12:16:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-21-universal-studios/</guid><description>&lt;p>Up early today for our last full day in America&amp;hellip; Left the hostel at 8.30am for Universal Studios, which we were both really excited about as we&amp;rsquo;d get to do a studio tour and a theme park in one. It was only a 15min drive away, and by the time we were through parking ($15) and walking through City Walk it was a little after 9am, the time the park opens. We bought our tickets which were quite expensive at $75 each.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/Xa9pFg06UHgExQ0hJ1cwkA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-0lBp69ov3C4/TiGbK0W3yYI/AAAAAAAAAY8/UEBP1XFOyCU/s400/IMGP1989.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
It was really quiet as we got there so early, and after walking through the gates a lady approached us and asked us if we could do a survey for her. We said yes iffily and answered a couple of questions and were then given queue jump pass for the studio tour! Had read last night that the best way to do the park if you arrive early is the studio tour, then the lower lot and finally the upper lot. So we headed for the tour and used our queue jump so had no wait. We boarded the tram and sat on the left (the best side to sit).
&lt;p>Began the studio tour by driving around all the currently used sound stages, most of them closed up looked like they were in use. Saw a few bits and pieces and went in to the King Kong 3D experience, it was incredible, best 3D we&amp;rsquo;ve ever seen. Didn&amp;rsquo;t realise until halfway through there were screens on both sides (King Kong was killing Dinosaurs oh yeah). Then we did the outdoor lots, the New York plot which looked great but didn&amp;rsquo;t get to go through it as they were preparing it for filming a new movie. Transformers 3 was just filmed there. After that drove past the famous cars from movies bit which was also really cool, every car would be followed by an ooh and aah. Saw the DeLorean from Back to the Future, jeeps from Jurassic Park and the good cars from fast and the furious.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/URU7SOJV9Ea5FRA0lKynDg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-eVp1AxaGAZ4/TiGak4bhmQI/AAAAAAAAAX0/M8VgyjpHqRI/s400/IMGP1909.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
Next we went to the set from Jaws with a fully functioning mechanical shark (the one they actually used in the movies). Wisteria Lane followed that, where they were actually filming when we drove past, saw a "Silence on set" sign which was cool. War of the Worlds plane crash set was insane, which we went to next. Had a real Boeing 747 smashed up as part of the set, looked very realistic, apparently a Pilot who flew over the set called in an emergency saying that there had been a plane crash haha. There was so  much stuff it could easily be a blog post just on the studio tour, Jimmy Kimmel did the video guide ("Have a Tramtastic Day!").
&lt;p>We walked down to the lower lots, which were surprisingly empty and went straight for the Jurassic Park ride. Wasn&amp;rsquo;t expecting much thought it was more of a child&amp;rsquo;s ride but the final drop was an 85ft vertical drop which scared the hell out of us and soaked us right through. Then we hopped over to The Mummy ride (feeling like we were kids again) put my bag into the fingerprint secured lockers (COOL). No queue at all, and surprised us again being so good. We went on it straight after with pretty much no queue the second time either. To be honest it was no where near as good the second time I think it is more of a shock factor ride.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After the thrill of Jurassic Park and The Mummy rides we headed over to the Cinnabon stand to get some snacks (my Cinnamon swirl was 850calories and delicious). It was getting a lot busier by this time and the queue for the Studio Tour was 60mins!  Hit up the House of Horrors after Cinnabon, was the biggest queue yet of nearly 10mins and half worth the wait.&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CvvYzz6SVq8cAy4eakYCgA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-MbTaOa9zTFk/TiGbDvKGDPI/AAAAAAAAAYk/d43ts82t_8M/s400/IMGP1978.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Could have been scary but there are so many people walking around you are never alone long enough to get frightened. I did get jumped out on by this weird mummy thing which made me poop myself but other than that was a walk through a dark house.  On to the Terminator 2: 3D show&amp;hellip;.Wow, first sign it was old was when Sarah remembers watching the trailer for it on the Terminator 2 VHS. Then on to the show - pretty much a joke. Everything was ancient, apart from the guy onstage who was supposed to be Arnold Schwarzenegger who looked nothing like him. Aftwerwards we went to Shrek 4D, where we got lucky and managed to join the back of the queue just as everyone started moving and got into the next showing. Was much, much better than the Terminator 2: 3D nonsense. Really funny with the weird moving seats (SPOILER).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Then the Special Effects Stage, got seats right at the front which was awesome, two classic American presenters bantering with each other. There was also Larry the hilarious stage hand which was apparently his &amp;ldquo;first day&amp;rdquo;. We were a bit nervous to be sat so close to the front when they started asking for volunteers but luckily there were lots of eager people in the audience, someone sat right behind us screamed for a chance and got chosen. They spoke about and demonstrated CGI, motion capture (was cool to see it being done), etc. Was a really good show, funny and informative. It was about 3.15 and we were aiming to leave at 4 so we had enough time to do one last thing  - The Simpsons Ride. The queue took 35mins but didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like it as there were tv&amp;rsquo;s everywhere showing The Simpsons so could watch whilst we waited. We weren&amp;rsquo;t really sure what the ride was and found it weird when the queue split and people were going upstairs as we were going downstairs. We ended up in a tiny room of 6 before getting on the ride. Won&amp;rsquo;t spoil it for anyone but we both really enjoyed it and was nothing like anything we&amp;rsquo;ve seen/been on before!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After the thrill of the park we headed to the shops for some last minute souvenir buying and a well needed rest. We went to Starbucks where we had the worst customer service&amp;hellip; Hardly any staff so a big queue, and the staff that were working weren&amp;rsquo;t really doing a lot and gave the wrong drink to one woman. Then we received the wrong drink too, and the woman was really rude about it, muttering to the other workers about it! Glad to get out of there and finish our coffees we headed back to the hostel. Didn&amp;rsquo;t stay long as it was around half 6 and didn&amp;rsquo;t want to leave packing too late. We found directions for the nearest Walmart - about 15mins away. When we arrived there it looked a bit scary, but found out it was right next to a police station. We bought lots of American snacks so we could bring some back with us, then went back to the hostel to find directions to In-n-out burger. We&amp;rsquo;d been looking forward to this for a while as we&amp;rsquo;d read such great reviews about it. And it definitely was the best fast food we&amp;rsquo;d had this holiday! There wasn&amp;rsquo;t much choice but didn&amp;rsquo;t need any more than it offered, was really fresh, great service, the fries were a bit weird compared to other places (they are cut in the store).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We went back to the hostel for the last time&amp;hellip; packed everything up which took quite a while. Both feeling sad to leave we went to sleep at about 12.30. Getting up earlier than originally planned as we are slightly worried about carmageddon!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 20- around la</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-20-around-la/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 12:15:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-20-around-la/</guid><description>&lt;p>The alarm woke us up this morning at 8am. We had a long day ahead of us darting around LA, so got ready quick and set off in the car. We headed straight for Hollywood that was only a few mins away, on the way we had a diversion, there were lots of police &amp;amp; fire trucks and they had closed a block off with flares lit on the floor. We were on Hollywood Blvd so looked for parking and went to Hollywood &amp;amp; Highland as the parking was only $2. We walked up to a higher level of the shopping centre for views of the Hollywood sign where we got a couple of pics before heading down to Starbucks for breakfast. We then carried our coffees on to the street where we walked up and back down looking at the stars on the floor.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/xoVNNS-eMI_l8gxRSMr0MA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-giseIEDP2zM/TiDvXdALIDI/AAAAAAAAAWE/mhNkBhIe1XE/s400/IMGP1811.JPG" height="400" width="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Got lots of photos of them including Jackie Chan, Bruce Lee and Michael Jackson. We continued past the Kodak Theatre (home of the Oscars) and up to Grauman's Chinese Theatre. I put my hands in Marilyn Monroe's imprints and Jon in Arnie's among others.
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/sn9QZSTfkMtv_-AWooK43A?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-T1sDqwHANwE/TiDvdau5x3I/AAAAAAAAAWI/5xOJNjium7s/s400/IMGP1823.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
There was also a Star Wars one where r2d2's wheels were imprinted. We continued to look at the stars, Jon wanted to find Will Smith's but didn't manage to. We considered a Star Homes Tour, but our parking only lasted 2 hours before it would start to get really expensive, so went back to the car for a little drive around ourselves.
&lt;p>We headed for Sunset Boulevard, passing firstly by the Capitol Records building. On Sunset Blvd we drove by the Comedy Store, Johnny Depp&amp;rsquo;s The Viper Room (where River Phoenix died), and Rainbow Bar &amp;amp; Grill. We drove in to Beverly Hills where the average house price is over $2.2million! Drove around looking at all the huge houses (well gates that lead to houses..) until we spotted a tour bus which we then sneekily followed for a bit. We took photos of the ones they took photos of but have no idea whose homes they were. At least one of them we knew was Elvis Presley&amp;rsquo;s as there was a door on the gate with his name carved all over it. We came back out on to Sunset Blvd and turned off at Bel Air, but as soon as we turned we saw a huge gate to get in and Jon quickly made a u-turn, didn&amp;rsquo;t wanna get stuck with security. We then decided to stop at the $1.3billion Getty Center, mainly because $1.3bn is a lot but also it&amp;rsquo;s meant to have some pretty nice views up there. Admission was free but parking cost $15. We rode the tram up to the top and had a look around some galleries, saw Van Gogh&amp;rsquo;s Irises, and went up to a view point. It was quite a clear day and so could see across to downtown and out to the Pacific. We were looking for lunch here but didn&amp;rsquo;t find anything we fancied so just bought a drink. We had an iced coffee which was horrible, just coffee with ice in it that made us both feel ill.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Carried on down Sunset, stopping for gas, until we reached the coast. We drove to Santa Monica pier and parked at a lot that cost $8 for the day. The weather was lovely and sunny, so we set out to the beach and on to the pier.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0b1aXwWeJ8TkvJaMMfUOYQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-EhvFLmOSUdo/TiDw5gPbRaI/AAAAAAAAAXQ/N1Gx8fKD4Gc/s400/IMGP1872.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We bought some hotdogs and a cinnamon pretzel as we were so hungry by this point. We took some pics including one of a sign marking the end of route 66. Walked down to the beach where there were lots of people exercising on the outdoor equipment (rings, rope, etc). We followed the boardwalk to Venice Beach where the path started to fill with stalls, with lots of weird looking people about. There were hippies, people trying to sell their music, random acts (like a man standing on a ladder one legged holding 2 fake snakes shouting about corporate America) and people with big muscles. We then came to Muscle Beach which was a bit disappointing, all concrete and tired looking. The stuff at Santa Monica looked a lot better. Walked out on to the beach to have a sit down and watch the waves crash, was nice to have a rest. After about half an hour we went back to the car and there were quite a few cars in the lot waiting for spaces. A woman asked us if we were leaving so we said yes and offered them our ticket (as you pay for the space) for $5, which she seemed very pleased with so we only ended up paying $3 which was good.
&lt;p>Drove back towards the hostel, making a few stops along the way. Firstly we pulled off in to UCLA which was huge and we couldn&amp;rsquo;t really find our way around (we were looking for their gift shop), so we left after only a few mins. I looked on the map for a shopping centre and spotted the Beverly Centre so decided to head there. We looked around but there wasn&amp;rsquo;t any good deals in any of the shops so went to the apple store so we could have a go googling other places to go. We found another one close by - Century City, so thought we&amp;rsquo;d stop there before it closed at 8pm. We left to go to the car park but must&amp;rsquo;ve taken the wrong escalators. We didn&amp;rsquo;t realise yet, so we paid for our ticket and attempted to find the car&amp;hellip; We couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it so were starting to panic as we knew we didn&amp;rsquo;t have long till our ticket would expire. We then realised we went down different escalators than the ones we came up, so had to find our way back through the mall and after around 10mins of rushing around we found it. We arrived at Century City but again there wasn&amp;rsquo;t any good sales so we just bought some socks as we had run out. It was just after 8 when we left, so we drove over to K-Mart which was a bit scary, and bought microwave pizzas and snacks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We arrived back at the hostel and cooked our pizzas and drank beer whilst watching some movies and writing up the blog. Sad this&amp;rsquo;ll be our last proper sleep in the US, but excited about tomorrow as we are going to Universal Studios Hollywood!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 19 - LA</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-19-la/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 12:11:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-19-la/</guid><description>&lt;p>Day 19, boohoo only 3 nights left in the states before we return home to the UK. Woke up at a reasonable 8am after another horrible nights sleep camping. (Can definitely conclude that after finishing all our camping, you either need to go for it 100% e.g. Buy an inflatable mattress and a camp stove, hammock etc or sleep in the car and spend nothing.) Walked down to the beach through an immaculately kept trail(NOT) and was pretty nice, really foggy though seems to take ages for the fog to clear especially the higher up you go.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/pyXAvxE6BF1IqPTyBgWD6g?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-6EUdOVOfRvM/Th8bsKA9Z3I/AAAAAAAAAVI/QBtxetRx9xc/s400/IMGP1779.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We packed up the tent for the last time and headed off before 10. Drove for miles through thick fog. A lot of road works where there had been rock slides and it had taken the road with it, so sometimes had to wait up to 20minutes to get through the single lanes. Sarah and I were planning what to do in L.A whilst waiting though so it wasn't much of a problem.
&lt;p>Made a detour to drive through San Luis Obispo and stopped at the famous Madonna Inn.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/7stvz8GOnQ2QjDwEgl1j-A?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Pms2cX5662s/Th8buzuyVFI/AAAAAAAAAVQ/-L0YJieXmpU/s400/IMGP1791.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
It has crazy décor with every room having a different theme, we just popped into the toilets as we had read that theses are something you should do if you are not staying at the hotel. Stopped off at McDonalds (again) for some snacks before hitting the road again. By the way, McDonalds really is that cheap, cheaper to buy food there than at a supermarket. $1 for a super large coke with 2 free refills against $1 for 900ml of powerade is no competition.
&lt;p>Carried on driving and stopped at Santa Barbara and Malibu(stacey). Got stuck in some bad traffic, just a taster of the carmageddon that will be coming on the day we leave. They are closing the 405 freeway which is the busiest road in L.A. The news has reported that you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t go out in your car as you will be jammed up for hours. Not looking forward to leaving even more so now that we are potentially going to be stuck in traffic trying to drop our car off and get to the airport.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Arrived at the orbit hostel after a few wrong turns and many turn arounds. Tried to check in and must have forgotten to read through the terms and conditions of this place as it was cash only and we only had a few bucks on us. Had to run across to a Bank of America that was down the street to withdraw some money. A second pin guess later and a dash down the street we had money and paid for our three nights. Not before the receptionist had to pop her head out of her office to say we had given her $20 to little&amp;hellip;whoops. Went up to the room to get showered ASAP as we were desperate to head out for some food and to have a proper look around L.A. No wifi signal in our room so once we were ready we popped to the communal area to use the wifi and do some checks before we headed out. Found Pink&amp;rsquo;s, a really famous hot dog stand just around the corner from us so  went and got in line.( It was huge, took around an hour to get served and eaten, but well worth the wait. I had a stretch chilli dog and Sarah had a cheese chilli dog. It was chilli as in mexican bean chilli not just hot sauce(never had anything like it on hot dogs before) and was awesome, super tasty would definitely go back again, reasonably priced too. The wall there was covered with famous peoples photos and signatures so must be popular with the celebrity locals.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/623pURgOCrnCIgi9wt8MbA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-2hY6jbisk88/Th8b6mCuDaI/AAAAAAAAAVo/8c_RurmvS78/s400/IMGP1800.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
From Pink's we headed straight to the grove shopping center not far from the orbit hostel. After a lot of searching we found the parking and where the cinema was (we planned on seeing transformers 3). Movie was due to start at 9.15 and we arrived into the cinema at 9.20, decided to risk it and get tickets for the 9.15 showing. Also got a medium popcorn(salty eugh) and a drink, made it in time for just after the start of the movie so we were pleased with our efforts. Movie wasn't great would have preffered to have a fire alarm go off after the first hour so everyone could leave thinking it was great. The last hour and a half were balls. Highlights of the cinema experience were A. Funny Americans doing what Americans do best laughing clapping and cheering in the movie. B. just how grand the cinema actually was, no tacky building here no sir, only the best for L.A.
&lt;p>Zoomed to the hostel to find no parking so risked it in a dodgy spot outside ( It was fine in the end) and had a well deserved sleep&amp;hellip;in a bed! Amazing how much you miss a bed not being in one for a night. Anywho its late and need some sleep after an action packed day, will try and write a blog post on it tomorrow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 18 - pacific coast</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-18-pacific-coast/</link><pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2011 12:10:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-18-pacific-coast/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today we were up at 8 to get showered and leave this lovely hotel. We were all packed up and ready by 9.30. We decided last night that we&amp;rsquo;d drive via Silicon Valley, as Jon wanted to see the Google headquarters there.So we left San Francisco and found the drive through a lot easier to when we first arrived. There was still a lot of fog around so was wet and cold outside. We came off the interstate at Mountain View, and followed Google&amp;rsquo;s directions until we reached &amp;lsquo;Google&amp;rsquo; which was the name of the street. We were looking for a big sign to get a photo of so we were searching around the huge offices. Was cool as we passed loads of google bikes, including a weird one with about 6 seats facing inwards in a circle to pedal and one at the front to steer. We also passed one building where we could see staff playing ping pong. Then we spotted a big sign next to a building which we guessed were the Android offices as outside was full of android stuff. So we stopped here for photos, noticing the staff passing us were casually on there way to work at 10.30 on their bikes with macbooks in the front baskets.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/kULdQz9MjzZAuAbmPA-qWQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-FFE5wB4_Xr0/Th8a9ndC4QI/AAAAAAAAATQ/f9uCRCFMiKs/s400/IMGP1594.JPG" height="400" width="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
After managing to find our way out, we stopped for food and gas. We first went to Krispy Kreme for 4 doughnuts which we ate before starting to feel a bit sick of sweet stuff, so we went across the road to McDonalds to get a double cheeseburger meal.It's crazy how many mcdonalds they must have here, whenever we're hungry and pull off a road we always manage to come across a mcdonalds. Back on the road we headed for Santa Cruz. Once we arrived we looked for parking by the boardwalk/pier. We drove up to one spot but found out it was $12, so we carried on and pulled into the meter parking just next to the lot. It was 25c for 10mins, which was all the quarters we had on us.. and the change machine wasn't working. So we thought we'd just stay for 10mins, and rushed over through the rides to the beach where the sun was shining. It was pretty busy, if we had longer we would've had a go on the roller coaster. We didn't have the time on us so quickly got back to the car to see the meter had expired so had to leave.
&lt;p>Carried on the drive until we hit Monterey, where we pulled off and parked in a garage at Cannery Row. We had a walk around here, and thought it&amp;rsquo;d be cool to go to the aquarium, but as it was expensive and we didn&amp;rsquo;t have much time we decided not to. We walked to the beach and could see sealions laying on the rocks, yay we managed to see some after theuy weren&amp;rsquo;t in San Fran. We saw a Ghiradelli shop and thought we had to go in and have the world famous sundae there, so we did whilst sitting out the back by the beach - yummmy!We then went to the next town, Carmel, where Clint Eastwood was once mayor. Searched around for &amp;lsquo;The Hog&amp;rsquo;s Breath&amp;rsquo; but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find it, so instead went to the beach where there were big waves, with warnings of how dangerous they&amp;rsquo;d be. We were then on the &amp;lsquo;best&amp;rsquo; park of the CA-1 (Cabrillo Hwy/PCH) so I decided to film this until it ran outta battery so around an hours worth which we&amp;rsquo;ll speed up once we&amp;rsquo;re back. The views along this road were amazing, the ocean was so blue. We stopped at lots of view points for photos.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/n6wB9Nm2BvlMdNacX1HXsg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-OSJjyYIaevg/Th8byL3wStI/AAAAAAAAAVc/hDfdGsEz4pM/s400/IMGP1638.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We were stuck behind 2 slow cars which was frustrating as they were doing 20 below the speed limit and you can't overtake. They weren't pulling into the pull out stops either.. We pulled off at a state park (can't remember name) and had to pay $10 to get in. We were looking for the waterfall that goes straight in to the Pacific Ocean (the only one that does) and after looking in my book discovered we were at the wrong place so exited straight away. Luckily our pass got us into the place we were looking for - Julia Pfeiffer. We parked up here and walked out to McWay Falls and got some pics. Didn't stay long as we were both hungry and thirsty.
&lt;p>Continued on the beautiful road until we saw a shop at Lucia. Bought firewood ($9), a croissant, cookie and water. The campground we are straying in doesn&amp;rsquo;t have drinking water. It was an expensive shop as there weren&amp;rsquo;t really any along the road. Tried to pay with Jons card but it kept declining it, the lady said when that message comes up it&amp;rsquo;s usually becuase of fraud. So we were both quite worried but knew we wouldn&amp;rsquo;t have internet till tomorrow so forgot about it and paid with cash.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We arrived at Kirk Creek Campground at 6.30pm, where we set up our tent for the last time in record speed. Lit the fire straight after too. The campsite was awesome, with views over the pacific ocean.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/MyCLQspLdS5M3WKvs7JTLQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-oKjaKYnktIU/Th8bhdMldKI/AAAAAAAAAUo/GwGIrBcLSj4/s400/IMGP1679.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
There was a bunny living at our site which was cute. We ate food around the fire, and chilled out drinking beer. We lit Jons cigar (thanks Bec) using the fire as we forgot to smoke it in Las Vegas. We watched the sunset from our beach which was lovely. It was cold here so stayed close to the fire until around 10pm when we went to the toilets which were scary as had no lights in them, and headed to bed. The tent was on grass this time so hoped for a better sleep, although we put the tent unknowingly over a huge lump which wouldn't help. Tomorrow is our last big drive to Los Angeles, which we are both excited and sad about!
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 17 - San fran sights</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-17-san-fran-sights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2011 12:09:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-17-san-fran-sights/</guid><description>&lt;p>After an amazing sleep we were up at 8am to shower and get ready for our busy day. We were all ready by 9, and had made lots of plans to fit in everything we wanted to see/do. We left and discovered how cold it was! We decided to go to the car to get some trousers and hoodies as shorts were a definite no. The fog was around so the air was wet and windy, felt good to get into some warmer clothes. We left for Lombard Street&amp;rsquo;s crookedest part which was just around the corner, where we encountered our first steep hill and wow it was steep. We made it to the bottom of the crooked part to get some pics, there were quite a few tourists here all looking tired from the walk. We continued up Lombard St where we planned to get a bus. However we were chatting away and didn&amp;rsquo;t realise how far we&amp;rsquo;d actually walked, so decided to just walk to Golden Gate Bridge instead of catching the bus. This was a 3.9mile walk (didn&amp;rsquo;t realise it was this long) but the views of the bay were fab. There wasn&amp;rsquo;t many tourists about  it was mainly joggers and people doing various exercises along the boardwalk. We picked up a hot chocolate as we were freezing which definitely helped. We finally made it to Fort Point and there were amazing views here, shame about the fog though.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/PmAEzQQZ-PJpIqC3QLF2xQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-1p38MSOcWw4/ThubxrrhbbI/AAAAAAAAAQ0/Ahu-6rqEl20/s400/IMGP1533.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
We nearly got splashed a few times by the waves which were coming up over the road.  We went in to the gift shop and bought a large coffee to warm us up some more before heading up to the bridge.
&lt;p>We took lots of photos of the bridge, but decided not to cross as we were cold and had lots more to do. We did a camera swap with a family from Los Angeles, took me a while to work out how to use their phone for their pic but managed it in the end. From here we caught a muni bus that would take us to the Golden Gate Park. It cost $2 for a transfer which means you can use any buses for 90mins (although ours lasted longer) which is a pretty good deal. The bus got quite crowded with lots of students from UCSF which is right near the park. Luckily we got off at the right stop and could see signs for the Japanese Tea Gardens which is where we were headed. The park was quite quiet as the weather wasn&amp;rsquo;t too good and it was still quite early, around 11.30. It&amp;rsquo;s huge though and we walked a lot here, our feet began to ache.. We got to the Japanese gardens but it cost $7 each so decided we&amp;rsquo;d rather the money to spend on food! We could see in though and it did look beautiful, maybe some other time.. We walked to the De Young Museum which currently had Picasso&amp;rsquo;s art inside, but was shut on a Monday so couldn&amp;rsquo;t get in. So we went to the Carousel which was built in 1912, and had a hotdog while watching it go round.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After refuelling on hotdog, we went out of the park to find a bus to Union Sq. We easily found the 21 trolley stop but just missed one so continued on until one came. The 21 stops at Alamo Sq too so we jumped off there to take some pics of the painted ladies, which looked really pretty.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/CaT4xQVkbU6GSOZokt7EoQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-z7FRazkbcPU/ThubzLlvCVI/AAAAAAAAARY/dL_K_1yA8jE/s400/IMGP1558.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
Caught the next bus which dropped us off at the Powell St cable car turnaround. Jon instantly recognized this area, so led us in to a mall where we stopped in A&amp;amp;F and Hollister, but as this was a central area the sales were only 30% off so didn't get anything. We walked around Union Sq. before noticing that it was nearly half 2 and our tickets ran out at 3. So it kinda went crazy as we rushed to Chinatown to have a little look and bought a souvenir before attempting to find a bus to Fisherman's Wharf. We arrived at the stop around 10 to, so we waited until 5 past but no bus... We had no more cash on us so couldn't catch the next bus if it ever arrived, so instead we decided to walk it.
&lt;p>We walked through Chinatown and up the hills past Coit Tower all the way to Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf, our feet were so tired. Headed straight for Boudin Bakery where we both had the &amp;lsquo;Best of Boudin&amp;rsquo; half sandwhich and soup in sourdough roll. I had grilled cheese and clam chowder, Jon had grilled cheese and chilli. We finally got to rest our feet although the floor was full of birds eating crumbs.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/U39hYW4z9gQI4tY5xVtVyw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-SId_U9-j-7o/Thub0WNFYjI/AAAAAAAAAR0/PoznbSYjoLI/s400/IMGP1574.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
The food was delicious and there was so much of it as always. After the well deserved rest we headed for one last stop before returning to the hotel for a rest. We went to Ghirardelli Sq. which was originally a chocolate factory now done up full of restaurants and shops. We of course headed straight for the Ghirardelli chocolate shop where we received a free sample which was delicious!
&lt;p>Our feet were now crying out for a lie down, so we walked back to the hotel. On the way Jon twisted his ankle pretty bad down a hill, which meant having to pretty much hop the rest of the way. Got back to the hotel and had a nap for an hour or so. Luckily Jon&amp;rsquo;s ankle was feeling a bit better after a rest as we had planned on eating out at Cafe Zoetrope. So at around 8ish we left, missed the turn but managed to find our way anyway as had kinda learnt the major roads now. Arrived at Francis Ford Coppola&amp;rsquo;s cafe, which was really nice but we felt a bit under-dressed. Was cool that it had a few of his awards on the wall and pictures from his movies. I had the Malfatti and Jon had the Tony Special Pizza, both were yummy! We walked the 15mins back to the hotel, but got to a big junction and walked back and forth 3 times crossing the same homeless guy until we conceded that we were lost. So we put some money in his pot and asked for directions to Mason St. Bless him, he was so nice and gave us the right directions so managed to get back fine.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Just gone 10pm now, feeling really tired. We worked out we&amp;rsquo;ve walked around 12.5miles today up and down the hills.. so we shall sleep well. Tomorrow we are hitting the road again down the pacific coast to Big Sur, will be staying at a lovely campground on the coast so may not be able to post till the 13th when we&amp;rsquo;ll be in our final destination (aww) Los Angeles!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 16 - San francisco</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-16-san-francisco/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 12:08:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-16-san-francisco/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today was the day we headed to San Francisco, yahoo. We slept in till 8 (usually up at 6 on a campground) and packed everything up and got ready to leave. We were ready by 9 so headed over to Curry village and bought a Yosemite bear bottle opener souvenir and some milk duds, &lt;span>&lt;span>mmm&lt;/span>&lt;/span> tasty.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hit the road at 9.30&lt;span>&lt;span>ish&lt;/span>&lt;/span> with a long day of driving ahead of us. We were both keeping our eyes peeled for bears but saw none. Boohoo. Did see a forest fire though as we were leaving the national park, was fully under control though and there were just tonnes of firefighters sat around not doing a lot. Was really cool to actually see one up close and personal, couldn&amp;rsquo;t get any good snaps, were moving quite quick and was quite smoky.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/SIQkL5ot-fAqEFuuOkyhZQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-FVmLj08NuT0/ThqkiPbuL4I/AAAAAAAAAN0/vVkFnFR1G4Y/s400/IMGP1318.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
On the way to the interstate the fuel light popped up and informed us we had 50miles till empty, we were still pretty much in the middle of nowhere (think it was a national forest) and hadn't gone past any gas stations since leaving the NP. Drove past 2 which we pulled in at and upon closer inspection found that they were closed down and looked pretty run down. Luckily found one though not too far after so was quite a relief. $3.89 a gallon which was our most expensive yet, but rather that than get stuck on the side of the road in front of a bunch of crazy guys on Harley Davidson's.
&lt;p>After we had been driving on the interstate for a while I started to get desperate for a wee, the road surface suddenly decided it was time to get super bumpy and was full of BIG potholes. This did not help my situation and so we took the first exit we could find ( miles away) but luckily America is full of &lt;span>&lt;span>McDonalds&lt;/span>&lt;/span> so we found one and stopped and got a burger and a drink and I had a well deserved wee. &lt;span>&lt;span>Aaaaahhhhhh&lt;/span>&lt;/span>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hit the worst traffic of our journey so far on the way to San Fran, the queues for the exits to Sacramento were huge and was crawling until we past the exit. Also was bad traffic at the tolls to go on the bay bridge. We paid the $5 toll, mostly in quarters as we had a pot full of them in the car &lt;span>&lt;span>hehe&lt;/span>&lt;/span>. On the bridge we managed to get our first glance of San Fran and it looked awesome, could see Alcatraz and the golden gate bridge. As we actually got into the city I got very stressed out with the driving, ran a red light by accident and then blocked a lane trying to turn left at a green light, got honked at and had to jump another red light &lt;span>&lt;span>yeehar&lt;/span>&lt;/span>.  We eventually made it to the hotel after a fair bit of stressing at around 3pm. Hotel looked gorgeous from the outside, classic &lt;span>&lt;span>san&lt;/span>&lt;/span> &lt;span>&lt;span>fran&lt;/span>&lt;/span> building. Checked in and brought all our bags up to the room, feels like home already and couldn&amp;rsquo;t be further from the tent we &lt;del>slept &lt;/del> tried to sleep in last night. We then paid $20 for 24hours of parking and drove round the block to park.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After a much needed shower and &amp;ldquo;freshen up&amp;rdquo; we headed down to fisherman&amp;rsquo;s wharf to check it out and have a wander around. Really busy, headed straight for the Boudin bakery to have a look and &lt;span>disappointed&lt;/span> to see no breakfast pizza on the menu! Still have soup in a roll though. Walked along to pier 39 to go look at the sea-lions, well some empty wooden floats that they usually sit on. Apparently they like it hot and go down south for their mating season, boohoo. Got some hot doughnuts and the smallest bottle of coke for the thirstiest people imaginable. $3 for 215ml.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Went ahead to board our boat to &amp;ldquo;The Rock&amp;rdquo;, was getting rather nippy now especially as we are used to the weather being above 100 most of the day, it was about 65 which is 50 less than the max we have experienced. After a thorough chilling and some great views we arrived on Alcatraz and followed the cool guide for a little while until we picked up our audio tours.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/KWIJ7XN9ETH09BkEQcXwvQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-_iRkv-oZe0M/ThqmAZMvcfI/AAAAAAAAAOU/Sfqy1p07Wvo/s400/IMGP1366.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
We followed the audio tour and it was fascinating, really enjoyed it and would definitely say its a must do. After we finished the tour we dropped the equipment back off and headed to the gift shop to pick up a few things. Whilst we were there we saw a tour about the escape from &lt;span>&lt;span>Alcatraz in 1962 that&lt;/span>&lt;/span> was about to start so we managed to catch it just in time. It was great, me and Sarah were desperate to watch the movie starring &lt;span>&lt;span>Clint&lt;/span>&lt;/span> &lt;span>&lt;span>Eastwood&lt;/span>&lt;/span> "Escape from &lt;span>&lt;span>Alcatraz&lt;/span>&lt;/span>" based on the true story the guide was telling. Me and Sarah think that they did escape as they are still on America's most wanted list, and the FBI have been searching for 20 years and have found nothing major. On the boat back to San Francisco we got to see the sunset over the Rock
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/nLejSnl7SWCB3UPVHQfYwQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Q9udKPgiKzE/ThqmCIPyIuI/AAAAAAAAAPE/E8sYkZD06eI/s400/IMGP1434.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
There was a crazy french kid taking a million photos and practically &lt;span>&lt;span>whooping&lt;/span>&lt;/span> to himself &lt;span>&lt;span>every time&lt;/span>&lt;/span> he got a good one. FRENCH PEOPLE ARE WEIRD. Either that or he had ADHD...oops.
&lt;p>Walked back to the hotel and stopped off at &lt;span>&lt;span>Safeway&lt;/span>&lt;/span> to grab some tea, weird black dude in the shop not buying anything just trying to chat up any single lady he could. Also the checkout lady (maybe a lady, could have been a guy) was really odd, super frantic at packing bags and sniffed the receipts before she gave them back&amp;hellip;We hurried home.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Off to sleep now so we can get up super early and have a full day exploring the city and get some good pics of the golden gate bridge.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 15 - Hiking &amp; soaking</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-15-hiking-soaking/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 12:07:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-15-hiking-soaking/</guid><description>&lt;p>So we did manage to get up at 6am this morning. After an OKish sleep (quite cool here) we were up, ready and into the car by 6.30. The roads were so quiet with only a few people about. We went straight for tunnel view but unfortunately as the sun was still quite low it was in the worst spot for photos so had to leave that for later. We carried on driving up to Glacier Point. Along the road 3 deer ran across the road in front of us, lots of chipmunks and a few californian ground squirrels - luckily we didn&amp;rsquo;t hit any. We arrived at Glacier Point (7214ft) and parked up before walking out to the viewpoint. We were the only ones there which was awesome, so could take lots of pics and have breakfast of trail mix whilst sitting on the rocks. We could see into the valley and all the famous points - Half dome, Yosemite falls, etc. Apparently this is a good place to spot bears but sadly we didn&amp;rsquo;t :(. After being harassed by chipmunks for our food we decided to drive to the trail head for sentinel dome, a moderate 2.2mile hike.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We parked up and headed out to the dome which would take us up to an elevation of 8100ft. It was a fantastic easy walk, with views all around. The view of Yosemite Falls in particular was amazing. At the top was also one of the worlds most famous dead trees - the Jeffrey Pine. After taking lots of photos we walked back to the car and drove off to Mariposa Grove. Here there are hundreds of giant Sequoias, where we went for a walk to the Grizzly Giant. The trees are HUGE, and the Grizzly Giant in particular is the 25th largest giant sequoia living today. It&amp;rsquo;s approx 209ft tall with a circumference of 96.5ft. It was hard to get pics of them as the photos just don&amp;rsquo;t show how big they really are.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/kgpjbmvkKU-sCxOF0Vptnw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-k0FuOy-Y2R8/Thqj9wTn54I/AAAAAAAAAM4/LyV7RgRmxcE/s400/IMGP1271.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
We decided to start heading back into the valley as the car park here was already full as it was a Saturday.
&lt;p>On the way we stopped off at Tunnel View again, this time the lot was full and there was a queue. People were just sat in their cars eating which was kinda frustrating as most people just wanna take a few pics as this is probably the most photographed spot of Yosemite. We carried on a couple hundred yards and luckily there was loads of parking spaces long the road so we stopped there and walked back up. We both had our photos and then we got a photo taken of the both us.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/ItYTXtVTsw6geCT9aZOpUA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-jGIWQtsRXIk/Thqj-oOrFnI/AAAAAAAAANI/qVemSTJvBzk/s400/IMGP1282.JPG" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
After a quick stop we got back in the car to go back to our tent for lunch which consisted of muffins.. The traffic started to build to a crawl, and after a while we saw signs saying lane closed as there were flood warnings. It took us nearly an hour to get through it all and in to the campground. We thought it was best to stay here for a while as it was way too busy to get anywhere.
&lt;p>At around 4pm we went off to the shuttle stop because we thought the traffic would be too bad to drive in. 3 buses full later we decided to give up and just drive as there was no chance we&amp;rsquo;d get on a bus anytime soon. Not such a good idea as the traffic was still really bad. We drove to the Ahwahnee Hotel, which is where Stanley Kubrick&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;The Shining&amp;rsquo; hotel was modelled on. We walked around and saw the huge fireplace and the creepy looking elevators. As we were leaving we heard some Americans chatting, saying that Prince William and Kate should come stay here on their tour.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We then went to Yosemite falls, the highest waterfall in the US and the 6th highest in the world (2425ft). We chose to do the 0.5m walk just to the lower falls as it was around 5pm and were getting hungry. This is a definite must do!! We got to the falls and it was so loud and the wind and spray was freeeezing!&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/6Xa0PY7eA59SDdEE20bfXA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-DM1p0gn8QJs/Thqkg8fQOgI/AAAAAAAAANg/SPiTHVF-Jfc/s400/IMGP1297.JPG" alt="" width="300" height="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
It was really busy which kinda sucked but we got some pictures before spotting people on the rocks right up to the waterfall. So yeah we decided to do the same.. which was amazing! We climbed over the rocks and were absolutely soaked through but was well worth it. Once we got back down we could finally hear again and as we were walking back to the car we were getting some odd/worried looks.
&lt;p>We got back to the tent to change in to some dry clothes before heading out to Curry village for some pizza. We paid $20 for a 16inch pizza. Was pretty busy here so had to eat it at our tent, with a warm beer thanks to the bear boxes getting so hot. After the feast of pizza we headed to bed early again at around 10pm. Could&amp;rsquo;ve spent a lot longer here exploring but off to San Francisco tomorrow which we are both excited about!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 14 - Yosemite NP</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-14-yosemite-np/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2011 12:06:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-14-yosemite-np/</guid><description>&lt;p>Up early this morning to make our journey to Yosemite. After getting ready we headed straight for McDonalds to get a 85c Super Large Coke which is soo good value, and 2 sausage mcmuffins. We then started the drive along the 395, alongside the Sierra Nevada&amp;rsquo;s which we&amp;rsquo;d soon be crossing. On the way we stopped off at Mono Lake.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/w4EA3LGhevfGgP4CABSmRg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-awPYShNnF3c/ThqivWlbk7I/AAAAAAAAALc/H9z5Nzndw0Q/s400/IMGP1135.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
It contains 78grams of salt per litre and is full of Tufa towers. To put that into comparison the sea has around 35grams per litre. We snapped some pics before getting on the Tioga Pass which would lead us into Yosemite.
&lt;p>The pass reaches an elevation of 9943ft over the Sierra&amp;rsquo;s so there was quite a lot of snow and the temp was a lot cooler in the low 60s. The views along the road were amazing, and the water in the lakes/rivers was so clear. We stopped at Toulomne Meadows where we went to the shop and had a little walk.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/s5FSEjv66jREnWXYtyDM2Q?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-K_k7XZJ4XoQ/Thqiv21yILI/AAAAAAAAALs/Ph-4jQxcztI/s400/IMGP1153.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
It was a lot busier here than any other national park. We drove down in to the Upper Pines campground, and as we were registering the ranger talked to us about bears and how we were to store our food etc before Jon signed the form to show that we had been informed. She told us that on this very morning there had been a bear incident in our campground! This campground was the busiest we had seen, although our spot was a big one but was mainly in the sun so we only really used a quarter of it. We set up camp and were both feeling realllly tired by the end of it.
&lt;p>We decided to drive to Curry village to see how much firewood was. Unfortunately it was something like $9 so thought we may as well just use our charcoal and have a bbq instead. We decided to take the shuttle to Yosemite village to have a look in their shop, which was a bit bigger but pretty much the same. The shops were very over priced, so we ended up buying some ice cream, breakfast sausages and rolls for our barbecue. The sausages were brown sugar and honey flavor but they were the only ones for less than $5. We went back to the campground and started the barbecue which was so much better than the one we had at the Grand Canyon!&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/8O_8zwKBZSYJ3eM1RH8mKg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-9vucZ7k_AtQ/Thqj7bAcazI/AAAAAAAAAMA/yDo_ow5qwN8/s400/IMGP1188.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We managed to cook 4 sausages at a time, and they were alright.. well I began to feel sick they were too sweet for me but Jon managed to eat them OK. We were knackered by the time we were done and played a few card games whilst drinking beers. We headed to bed at about 9pm lol as we were falling asleep and planned on waking up at 6am so we could get out before all the tourists were around and to hopefully spot a bear...
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 13- Death valley</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-13-death-valley/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2011 12:04:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-13-death-valley/</guid><description>&lt;p>We planned to get up early today so wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be in Death Valley at the hottest part of the day, but we didn&amp;rsquo;t wake up till 9 and had a few things to do in Vegas before we left. So we quickly showered and packed, then popped across the road to Caesar&amp;rsquo;s to the gift shop. Had to wait for it to open at 10 and bought a few things. We returned to the hotel and checked out. We found out last night that there was a shopping center which had the 50% of red line sales out of town called town square, so decided we&amp;rsquo;d head there before hitting the road. Started off by driving north up the strip instead of south, but once we had turned around it didn&amp;rsquo;t take long to get there. It was really quiet, and we stopped in Hollister first. There were a lot of empty shelves so we were glad we had bought so much back in Flagstaff. Jon managed to get a couple more things though. We went to A&amp;amp;F but the 50% off part was rubbish so didn&amp;rsquo;t get anything. Also pretty much everything that wasn&amp;rsquo;t on sale had a tag on it saying &amp;ldquo;not for sale&amp;rdquo;, weird. We then filled up the tank and bought some snacks, making sure we had enough to get us through Death Valley.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We drove the &amp;rsquo;local&amp;rsquo; route, passing through Pahrump and into the valley.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?feat=embedwebsite#5626824955274887314">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-BryRbyKlh_o/ThZ_fBB2gJI/AAAAAAAAAJc/6v9Bv5RJs0U/s400/IMGP1025.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We were now in California where we will stay for the rest of our trip. The temperature was starting to rise, although in the distance were big rain clouds. The views were amazing, and we stopped off at Zabriskie point for our first view over the valley. It was a short walk up a hill to the viewpoint, totally worth it though and we snapped some pics at the top. The sun was really hot, but we were expecting it to feel alot hotter, we must be kinda getting used to it I guess lol. We got back in to the car, and decided we'd take the drive down to Badwater Basin, the hottest, driest and lowest place in the US (282ft below sea level)! The temp reached a max. of 116 even with clouds around. We arrived at Badwater and it felt alot hotter here. There were quite a lot of people about which felt good, wouldn't wanna be here on our own incase anything happened! We were suprised to see a pool of water here, but apparently that's the reason this is called badwater - as a man tried to get his mule to drink from the water but it refused. The salt flats were so white and you could see the heat radiating off the floor. Took some pics as we walked out onto the flats, started to get really hot so decided to walk back to get in to the air con.
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/0Tv13x461S4oUwOCKAd8Ww?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-VWqfsLbM3qs/ThZ_umbGeWI/AAAAAAAAAKE/9G7YKPsrWp4/s400/IMGP1047.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Back on the road, we headed off to artist's drive, a one-way road which was pretty fun - lots of dips and turns. Stopped at artist's pallette where there are so many different colours on the rocks. We continued to drive through Death valley before stopping off at Stovepipe Wells to fill up on drinks. For me Death Valley is a definite must do - the scenery is awesome and the whole drive has been the best so far.
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/LMxki_nCwQKnfJjWdD8mJg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-a3w477Fh0wc/ThaAkJ_ys1I/AAAAAAAAAKs/zPmC14U0XjI/s400/IMGP1110.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Heading out of death valley and up over the mountains the temp was beginning to drop. Funny moment when a pickup truck overtook us and a guy was sat in the back looking like a hillbilly. The clouds were getting closer and then it started to rain in the desert! We saw signs for flooding so were a bit worried but luckily it wasn't too deep so could drive through fine. Passed through Lone Pine which looked like a cool town, from here you can see Mt. Whitney  the highest point it the US at 14505ft. Crazy to see the lowest point then the highest within a couple hours! After a long driving day (around 360miles) we arrived in Bishop and looked around for a motel. Sat in our room now at TownHouse Motel, it's like a granny cabin but quite big for the price.
We have now passed the 2000mile mark today. Don't like to think we are over halfway now... have so much more to look forward to - off to Yosemite tomorrow! May not have internet then till the 10th when we'll be in San Fran :D Hopefully by then we'll have seen a bear(but not too close), fingers crossed!
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 12 - Guns and sunbathing</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-12-guns-and-sunbathing/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 12:03:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-12-guns-and-sunbathing/</guid><description>&lt;p>We woke up late(8.30am being late) and had a leisurely morning pop tarts in bed etc. Got showered and had a spur of the moment decision to go to the gun range. On our way there I got a bit nervous and it wasn&amp;rsquo;t helped by the fact that when we pulled up outside there was a protest going on against the Gun Store.(Crazy mexicans)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Decided on the Gun Store package which was to shoot a Sig Sauer P226 and a H&amp;amp;K MP5, 2 targets and a T-shirt for $99. We paid and then noticed the queue which was HUGE. It took us about 2 hours to get to the front, we filled the time by spying on other peoples conversations (quite interesting one behind us with a woman doing a similar trip to us and then chatting about what guns they owned..to put it in perspective the one lady was short and skinny and the other was a 16 year old girl&amp;hellip;). Was definitely worth the wait, really enjoyed it. People were super friendly and couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it more don&amp;rsquo;t be nervous you should do it. I can tell even Sarah was thinking about having a go. As you can see from her trigger finger happy photo :)&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/1ZzmWSENi8V0i5F7PZDILQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-8ZFuB_HWGXk/ThUYeLKgnSI/AAAAAAAAAHg/fXkBoLxOs6o/s400/IMGP0963.jpg" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/A2xSaiamJTPZ5A8OGsG4Zw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-_rQgKQ5HvWE/ThUYjz1bytI/AAAAAAAAAIA/qNITQd_P_2Y/s400/IMGP0964.jpg" alt="" width="400" height="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u6--qfZ_-Sw" target="_blank">Video of me shooting H&amp;amp;K MP5&lt;/a>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5j7q8gI7ZFI" target="_blank">Video of me shooting Sig Sauer P226 Pistol&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By the time we were out and back at the hotel it was 2pm. It was Sarah&amp;rsquo;s turn to choose what to do, and she decided to hang out at the Flamingo pool. On our way we stopped at O&amp;rsquo;Sheas and got a $3 beer and hot dog each. Couldn&amp;rsquo;t bring outside beer into the pool area though so had to down it outside. Went in, grabbed some towels and found some loungers. Was really busy and loads of drunk people about. Funny booty shaking contest at the other side of the pool. We could just hear what was going on which was hilarious, some american lady wooping left right and center and crowds cheering the people on. Went into the pool too which was super refreshing and nice and cold, went under the waterfall (yes it had a waterfall) it was awesome. Sunbathed for the next couple of hours listening to the loud music playing on the speakers. As we were about to leave a big fat man (probably british) was dragged out of the pool by a lifeguard because he was falling asleep in the pool. His incredibly sunburnt friend was trying to get him to leave but he was lying on a lounger swearing at people (funny).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We went back to the hotel to shower and get ready to go out for a meal. We went for a wander but couldn&amp;rsquo;t find anywhere that we fancied so we went back to our room to look for places that were recommended. Decided on serendipty 3 in Ceasars. Went over and had to wait half hour for a table. Had a really weird waiter, either he had a funny sense of humour or he was depressed and hated his job. On the up side the food was gorgeous, I had &amp;ldquo;the full monty&amp;rdquo; sandwich with steak fries and Sarah had the BBQ chicken pizza. For dessert we shared the frozzzen hot chocolate which is what the place is known for, was totally worth it. Even though we were totally stuffed we managed to pretty much finish it.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width: auto;">
&lt;tbody>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?feat=embedwebsite#5626824848131979858">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-4eAEYuTCEuo/ThZ_Yx4_elI/AAAAAAAAAI8/bGZorASGnZQ/s400/IMGP0980.JPG" alt="" width="300" height="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;tr>
&lt;td style="font-family: arial,sans-serif; font-size: 11px; text-align: right;">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>
&lt;/tr>
&lt;/tbody>
&lt;/table>
Whilst we were eating it looked like they were setting up a film set with a few cameras and lighting. Will have to keep an eye out for any tv shows, movies or music videos filmed in serendipity 3 las vegas.
Went to watch the Bellagio fountains again and headed back to the hotel via some street acts (Little Elvis, Michael Jackson and las vegas junk drummers who were quite good). Fell straight to sleep which was good as we had a long drive ahead of us the next day.
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 11 - Vegas Baby</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-11-vegas-baby/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2011 12:02:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-11-vegas-baby/</guid><description>&lt;p>Woke up early 6am (7am mountain time) after a somewhat terrible sleep. Managed to be 100 degrees even through a thunderstorm last night. Feeling a bit grotty we decided to head straight to vegas to get showered and to get some junky vegas food. Drove through the Vegas strip and arrived in Las Vegas around 11am then checked our booking and saw check in was 4pm&amp;hellip;Went along and tried to check in, luckily she said we could check in 12.30pm which only left an hour and half before showers and food. Went a bit crazy and blew $1 on the slots, lost it all. We crazy.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/SRO7tndKms5KjUAt1WsPqw?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Y09G6J9f1Y4/ThSPnkESgNI/AAAAAAAAAEs/lChDIjvdw1c/s400/IMGP0870.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Came back and checked in at 12.30, room was nice can see the Bellagio fountains from our room. For $35 it's a bargain location-wize. We finally had our showers, and feeling fresh we decided to get out on to the strip. We went casino-hopping, which meant that we ended up walking more here than we did in Zion or Bryce. We stopped in at: The Venetian, Wynn Las Vegas, Treasure Island, Mirage, Caesar's Palace, Bellagio, NY-NY, Excalibur, Luxor, MGM Grand and Paris.
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/S9Mervf7j5Kmo3fIsh4wig?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh5.googleusercontent.com/-Ii-PBNcn-j0/ThSPo8HRBhI/AAAAAAAAAE0/uFiaYVe3T_Q/s400/IMGP0876.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
The casino's were HUGE, and each of them had something a bit crazy going on. Like The Venetian with it's gondola rides, MGM Grand having a lion habitat and Caesar's Palace's Forum Fountain Show (bizarre!!). Walking from casino to casino wasn't very pleasant - it was so humid. On every street corner there were crazy little Mexican people handing out escort cards. Whenever I refused a card they'd try and offer it to Sarah! Our feet were killing by the time we'd been in them all, and had been walking around till 7.30, so we went back to our hotel room to rest our feet for half an hour. We started to get hungry so had a think of where to eat and decided on the Cheesecake Factory in Caesar's.
&lt;p>At 8pm we left for Caesar&amp;rsquo;s, the whole strip was lit up and the streets were packed. Just before we left we grabbed some dollar margaritas which were half frozen, basically slushies (50% tequila, 29% Triple Sec, 21% fresh lime or lemon juice). Very strong, I think all the soda was frozen and it was just ice cold tequila with a hint of lemon. We headed straight for the cheesecake factory as it was quite late and we weren&amp;rsquo;t sure if we would get a table. Was busy when we arrived but only a 25 minute wait. Spent that in the apple shop using their laptops and free internet hehe.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At 9.15pm we were seated at our table. We were given the menu&amp;hellip;.400 different choices, luckily they gave us a specials menu which we both ordered from. I had the Salisbury steak with mashed potato. Sarah had the chicken something or other it was nice though. The portion sizes were HUGE Sarah only managed half before she started feeling ill from being so full. That meant I had to try and not only finish my ridiculously huge steak but try and eat her chicken pesto parma ham pasta stuff. I tried&amp;hellip;and failed. The main reason we went was for cheesecake but we were way too full to eat more. We think we might head there tomorrow instead to get some, looks super tasty. We were both super tired after our meal but managed to stay awake to watch the Bellagio fountains, they were spectacular. The final blast was worth the wait, I imagine it takes the 15minutes between shows just to charge up the pumps for the final blast. Was also super cheesy, people clapped&amp;hellip;just like at sunset in the grand canyon.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/6n8eE8kr6Wn-6-HmuG71IQ?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-QvAhsk59sHc/ThSQBcdNexI/AAAAAAAAAGI/EVOo5ji4Dos/s400/IMGP0928.JPG" height="400" width="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
Half asleep we headed back to the hotel and conked out for the night excited for a full day in vegas tomorrow.
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 10 - Zion</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-10-zion/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2011 12:01:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-10-zion/</guid><description>&lt;p>Happy July 4th!! We were up quite early this morning and realised that since we were in Utah it was Mountain Time so an hour ahead. A much better sleep here as it was a lot cooler than the Grand Canyon. We packed up the tent and drove over to the general store, where we had showers and washed our clothes. Then off we went for a much shorter drive to Zion. We passed through lots of towns, which were full of US flags and lots of people hanging out in their front gardens. We drove on the Zion-Mt. Carmel Highway which was fantastic! The road was really busy due to it being July 4th and so the parking for the Overlook Trail was full so unfortunately couldn&amp;rsquo;t do that. We drove through the 1.1mile tunnel which was cool, before heading down in to the canyon and in to Zion NP.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/AolfhMYn3_fbTQSoLxSyBA?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh4.googleusercontent.com/-GfKFrRycnKg/ThSO6teRV8I/AAAAAAAAADE/D6bWW4HDx00/s400/IMGP0790.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We decided to go straight to Watchman Campground to check-in, but we were told that our site still wasn't empty so had to wait till 12 (about 15mins). So we went in to the town of Springdale, and popped in to a supermarket where we bought bread, cooked sausage, pringles and gatorade. We then went to the campground and put up our tent. We were on site 33, but wished we were on 31 as this had a huge rock and had a lot more shade. The floor was made of gravel, and so when we tried to peg our tent down we were just hitting rock so had to leave it unpegged. After putting the tent up we heard rustling in the bushes and out came a deer! There were loads of ants climbing up our legs so decided to leave and get the shuttle bus in to the canyon as it's closed to cars during the summer.
&lt;p>The shuttle ride was boiling hot, no air con and crowded&amp;hellip; It felt like driving through Jurassic Park the scenery was amazing. There was an audio commentary on the bus, which stated that the sandstone cliffs here were the highest in the world. We got off at the last stop - the Temple of Sinawava. This was where the trailhead for the River Walk began, an easy 2.2mile walk along the Virgin River.&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/9YluI-dnQ7TGnohwxnmARg?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh6.googleusercontent.com/-4ElhvvfAktM/ThSPBNnJ7TI/AAAAAAAAADg/PUX4lPnQIx8/s400/IMGP0809.JPG" height="400" width="300" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
At the end of the hike the trail for the Narrows begins. We would have loved to do this one, but didn't have the right clothes/shoes. It's a hike through the river, and some points you'd have to swim through. It was very busy here so we quickly got our feet in to the water before walking barefoot to a quieter spot on the way back. There were loads of lizards along the way, and lots of squirrels running along the sand.
&lt;p>We then got the shuttle to Weeping Rock, and walked the 0.4mile trail. We were really hot, the air was so humid. Once we got to the top we were so glad we did this trail. Water was falling off the rock above us and we stood underneath and got soaked - so refreshing!&lt;/p>
&lt;table style="width:auto;">&lt;tr>&lt;td>&lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/lh/photo/TiIwGeTYS6wsqAD0N6FX-w?feat=embedwebsite">&lt;img src="https://lh3.googleusercontent.com/-Q5DMfhgTHn0/ThSPEtv0eRI/AAAAAAAAAD0/APkVHJELYm0/s400/IMGP0825.JPG" height="300" width="400" />&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;tr>&lt;td style="font-family:arial,sans-serif; font-size:11px; text-align:right">From &lt;a href="https://picasaweb.google.com/jonfry22/RoadTripUSA?authuser=0&amp;feat=embedwebsite">Road Trip USA&lt;/a>&lt;/td>&lt;/tr>&lt;/table>
We caught the bus again and got off at Zion Lodge and walked the Lower Emerald Pool Trail (1.2miles) to more waterfalls which were lovely. We were really tired after this, so went back to our tent where we discovered it was half 5 and 100 degrees. No wonder we were feeling so dead! It felt so hot at our site so we decided to get in the car and drive to Springdale. We were feeling a bit hungry so went for food at Wildcat Willies Ranch Grill &amp;amp; Saloon. We both had the Buffalo Meatloaf which was SO good, and the staff here were really nice. We wanted to stay in the cool, but decided to head back as it was getting dark.
&lt;p>We played a few card games, before heading in to our baking tent.. We heard a few fireworks, but sadly no fireworks/fires/charcoal were allowed in the park, they told us it was because of the risk of fire spreading. We managed to fall asleep with the tent open, but was woken up during the night by really loud thunder. It got worse and I had read yesterday to follow the 30/30 rule - if you can&amp;rsquo;t count to 30 between lightning and thunder then seek shelter. Well, after the first bit of thunder that woke us up we saw lightning and only managed to count to 1 before thunder. People were getting in there cars so we made a dash for ours too. Quite embarrasing when after it passed our car alarm went off whilst we were in the car! We decided to get back in to our tent when everyone else did, and managed to get back to sleep. Tomorrow we are off to VEGAS!!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 9 - bryce canyon</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-9-bryce-canyon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2011 12:00:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-9-bryce-canyon/</guid><description>&lt;p>Finally had a nice nights sleep at the motel 6. Aircon was quite noisy but rather that than frazzle, also noisy german baby grr. Got up showered and had breakfast of the stickiest cinnamon swirls in the world and pop-tarts. After a full re-arrange of the luggage and the boot, we headed off to horseshoe bend. It was a 3/4mile walk through hot sand (only found this out halfway up the hill and I was wearing flip-flops). Got there in the end and was a fantastic view. Doesn&amp;rsquo;t look that big in the photo but if you look closely you can see a boat on the river, and that shows you just how big it was. On our way back we were both dead and Sarah got stung by a mysterious black demon.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5908099952/" title="IMGP0669 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6033/5908099952_0e1ba4b2e0.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0669">&lt;/a>
We headed off to the Glen Canyon Dam, and stopped off quickly to take some snaps. We weren&amp;rsquo;t there for very long but that&amp;rsquo;s all it took to make us extremely jealous of all the people with boats and jet-skis.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Next we were off to Bryce Canyon NP. Drove along the scenic byway, saw alot of horses, wild deer and llama things. Arrived at the campground in Bryce, had lost our booking info so didn&amp;rsquo;t know what plot number we were at so had to drive round the whole campground searching for &amp;lsquo;fry&amp;rsquo;. It was on the last loop we checked, so parked up and set up camp. As we were setting up the tent there was extremely loud thunder and black clouds overhead. Read that Bryce is one of the most concentrated lightning storm areas in the US.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We drove down to Rainbow Point and got out for our first look of the canyon. Looked amazing, couldn&amp;rsquo;t wait to get down into the canyon and have a proper look around. Drove back down the from the top stopping at all the view points.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5908101644/" title="IMGP0728 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6009/5908101644_077eb6af16.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0728">&lt;/a>
Onto the highlight of the trip to Bryce, called the &amp;lsquo;World&amp;rsquo;s best 3 mile hike&amp;rsquo; (Navajo/Queens Trail) we were both pretty tired starting the hike, but within 10mins we were both buzzing down the canyon. Whether that was the gorgeous scenery or the sketchy american energy drink we had, its anyone&amp;rsquo;s guess.. (the drink&amp;rsquo;s ingredients were a list of e-numbers + caffeine). After we got down the steep part of the hike it started to rain pretty heavily for a bit so alot of people returned back up. So glad we didn&amp;rsquo;t, and it meant not many people were out walking. But its safe to say it was an amazing hike, couldn&amp;rsquo;t recommend it more, was the best day so far in the U.S. Seemed like every photo was a great photo and round every corner was something that would make you say &amp;ldquo;WOWWWWWW&amp;rdquo;.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5908104582/" title="IMGP0766 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6060/5908104582_6f9bb76178.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0766">&lt;/a>
Went back to the tent for a rest and headed straight out to the general store for some food. Didn&amp;rsquo;t really have anything that we fancied so went back to the tent for a hearty dinner&amp;hellip;Cap&amp;rsquo;n Crunch with warm milk. Mm mm mmmmmmm. It took all of one spoon to make me ditch it and have a pop tart. Black clouds were looming overhead so were doubtful we would wake up dry. Tomorrow onto Zion, fingers crossed in one piece.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 8 - monument valley</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-8-monument-valley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 12:00:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-8-monument-valley/</guid><description>&lt;p>The alarm went off at 3.30am this morning. So I snoozed it for 10mins but couldn&amp;rsquo;t get back to sleep so decided to have a look at the sunrise info. which is when I realised I had set the alarm an hour early. Luckily Jon had already fallen back to sleep, but unfortunately I couldn&amp;rsquo;t. The people in the pitch next to ours were up and I could hear them packing their tent away. I decided to look at a map and plan out where we&amp;rsquo;d go for sunrise. I read that Yaki Point was a good spot, but this was only accessible via shuttle bus and the last bus before sunrise was at 4.45am. So I woke Jon up at about 20past and we rushed to get ready in time. We drove down to the visitor centre where we&amp;rsquo;d catch the bus, but only had 1min to get from the car to the bus in the dark with no clue where we were. We were running around trying to find it and fortunately got there just in time. The sunrise was beautiful and a lot quieter than sunset, with just a couple of photographers set up. My camera battery only had 1 bar left so couldn&amp;rsquo;t take many pics/videos.
&lt;a title="IMGP0606 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895655027/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5277/5895655027_9e86e44778.jpg" alt="IMGP0606" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
We caught the bus back to the car and proceeded to the campground where we began to pack up. We had begun to live out of the boot with one suitcase practically empty so had to organize it all as there wasn&amp;rsquo;t really any space left. It took a while to get the tent down and packed and sort our stuff out, but we finally hit the road at 7ish. We were looking out for elk and mountain lions but didn&amp;rsquo;t manage to spot any. We drove on long stretches of 2 lane highways, heading NE towards Monument Valley. We stopped off at a town called Tuba City at a McDonalds. There were a lot of Navajo people around here. We bought 3 sausage mcmuffins, a hash brown and a large coke for $5, and used the free wi-fi. We filled up on gas, and drove on before stopping for a toilet break at McDonalds in Kayenta.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Off we went again, where we caught our first glimpses of Monument Valley. The temp. was now around 100 so was really hot when out of the car. We crossed the Utah border - making that our 4th state we&amp;rsquo;ve visited. We paid the $5 per person charge to enter Monument Valley, and it was well worth it.
&lt;a title="IMGP0624 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895655383/">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6052/5895655383_b0fabe8512.jpg" alt="IMGP0624" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
The sand was so bright and the views were fantastic. We took loads of pics here trying out different poses, trying to capture a John Wayne pose which we never could really achieve. I mean, what exactly is a John Wayne pose? We popped into the Visitor Center where we learnt about the Navajo tribe and how their native language helped with coding in World War 2.
&lt;a title="IMGP0628 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895655579/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5316/5895655579_bc0981fb10.jpg" alt="IMGP0628" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
We couldn&amp;rsquo;t spend too long here as we were so tired from waking up so early and the heat wasn&amp;rsquo;t helping either. We left just before lunch, and stopped at our 3rd McDonalds of the day where we had 20 McNuggets, a sundae and another large coke for just $7.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were now on the final stretch of today&amp;rsquo;s journey to Page. The scenery was really good along this route, and we drove along listening to Ricky Gervais&amp;rsquo; Podcasts. Coming in to Page we could see Lake Powell, which is a man-made reservoir and is the second largest in the US. We hadn&amp;rsquo;t made reservations to stay here, and unfortunately alot of places where booked out or quite expensive as it&amp;rsquo;s July 4th weekend. We finally found a motel 6 which was charging a reasonable rate. We put our cases into our room, took a shower then headed to the pool. The water was freezing but so refreshing. We&amp;rsquo;ve just come in from shopping at Walmart, where we bought our dinner and food for tomorrow. It&amp;rsquo;s 94 fahrenheit here and it&amp;rsquo;s 8.30pm, lovelyy.
&lt;a title="IMGP0662 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5896223974/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5316/5896223974_53bde4a479.jpg" alt="IMGP0662" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
We&amp;rsquo;ll be visiting Horseshoe bend and the Glen Canyon Dam before we go to Bryce Canyon where we&amp;rsquo;ll stay the night. Again, may not be on for a couple of days as camping for the next 2 nights, we&amp;rsquo;ll be in Vegas on the 5th though so will definitely be on then for an update. Not looking good in terms of weather after today&amp;rsquo;s hottest day of the year so far - storms are coming!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 7 - day in the canyon</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-7-day-in-the-canyon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 11:58:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-7-day-in-the-canyon/</guid><description>&lt;p>Woke up this morning to the sound of some kids smashing rocks together in the spot next to our tent at approx. 5.30am&amp;hellip; Had an OK sleep, the floor was pretty hard and it got quite cold during the night (we left the inner door open). As we couldn&amp;rsquo;t get back to sleep we decided to get up and have some lucky charms for breakfast. As I was going to the car to get something outta the boot I spotted a deer about 10foot away. We managed to get some pictures as it strolled past our pitch eating the plants, was so cool. We then went for a well needed shower which cost $2 each.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5896221350/" title="IMGP0466 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6050/5896221350_53ec0ec850.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0466">&lt;/a>
Once we were ready we jumped in the car with 2ltrs of water and a few crisps we had left over. We drove and parked at the Bright Angel Trailhead. By this time it was 8.45am and the sun was already getting hot. As we didn&amp;rsquo;t have much food with us and we&amp;rsquo;d left it quite late we only decided to go as far as the 1.5mile house. The walk down was nice and easy, with quite a lot of spots of shade, as the trail made switchbacks down the canyon travelling along a fault line. There were spectacular views all the way down, with lots of squirrels following us hoping for some food.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5896221612/" title="IMGP0471 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5156/5896221612_12015d2abe.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0471">&lt;/a>
As you travel further into the canyon the temperature starts to rise so by the time we got there we were starting to feel the heat. They had restrooms and water here so we refilled our bottles before making the ascent back up. We were originally planning on following the trail until the Indian Garden, but as the temp was so high it wasn&amp;rsquo;t advised. Apparently there would be no shade if we carried on further, which did not sound good! The way up was alot harder, but whenever there was a spot of shade we&amp;rsquo;d take a break and have some water. We also passed a group of Mormons which was quite cool. It was around 11am by the time we got to the top, and we felt good that we managed to at least hike a bit into the canyon.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were really hungry at this point so we went to the village and had a pizza in the air conditioned building, which made us feel a lot more energised. We then went to the tent and chilled out for a couple of hours. Our tent&amp;rsquo;s in partial shade, and we wanted to stay out of the sun during the hottest part of the day. We bought a pack of cards at the shop and played some games (including snap lol), and read some of our books.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At around 3.30, we drove out back to the Bright Angel Trailhead to park there as a lot of people park along the road or at the designated car parks. But this spot is as close as you can get to the red shuttle route, with lots of free spaces. We decided we were going to take this bus and jump off at all the points along the way. This route isn&amp;rsquo;t driveable during the summer and so using the bus is the only way (other than walking) to see it all. We stopped off at each point, took loads of photos, then caught the next bus.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895654369/" title="IMGP0532 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5234/5895654369_37b5ca0224.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0532">&lt;/a>
The views were breath-taking, and at some of the stops we were the only ones there! Our favourite stop was Pima Point. We continued this all the way to Hermit&amp;rsquo;s rest, before getting the bus back to the transfer stop and driving back to the campground.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was about 6pm by the time we got back, so we quickly lit the charcoal. Unfortunately they stopped allowing log fires the day we got here (due to it being summer so dry). We then waited&amp;hellip; and waited&amp;hellip; and decided to put in another firelighter. I think we were kinda impatient, but this was only because it was getting dark and we were trying to boil pasta and the water was still lukewarm 40mins after we started. It was just after sunset by the time it was all cooked, so we wolfed it down just before it was dark. We then headed to sleep as we wanted to be up in time to catch sunrise at 4.14am&amp;hellip; well it was actually 5.14am but I didn&amp;rsquo;t realise this yet.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 6 - grand canyon</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-6-grand-canyon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 11:57:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-6-grand-canyon/</guid><description>&lt;p>After a surprisingly good sleep we headed over to the Galaxy Diner. This was a 50s style diner that the Chinese guy recommended, but we&amp;rsquo;d also seen a couple of tourists wearing t-shirts from there yesterday. I had waffles with bacon and eggs, Sarah had french toast with sausages and eggs. Was funny when the waitress asked how I&amp;rsquo;d like my eggs, and I responded with a blank look (me and Sarah both thinking cooked), turns out scrambled was an acceptable answer. They both came with 2 pots of maple syrup each, so we were stuffed by the time we finished and started us off well for the day.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We then headed over to Fry&amp;rsquo;s Groceries (woohoo!) to do our shopping for camping, we picked up our first beer in America - 30 cans of Budweiser for $17 not bad at all! We bought minced beef, pasta and pasta sauce to cook on the fire (Bad idea..). Then queued to get gas again at Fry&amp;rsquo;s, got hustled out of every space we were waiting for. Not going to argue with a Texan with a HUGE truck.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Started the drive to Grand Canyon and what a drive it was. Stopped at Cameron Trading Post about half way through, was a nice place but super touristy and thus quite expensive. On walk back to car to carry on to Grand Canyon noticed a tumbleweed stuck in the grill, thought it would be a good idea to take it out, picked it up and BAM prickle (got swollen boohoo).
&lt;a title="IMGP0615 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895655185/">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6007/5895655185_844a19c905.jpg" alt="IMGP0615" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
We drove along the desert view trail stopping off on all the view points into the Canyon. We stopped for a picnic halfway in the cool of some trees, it was super hot. A lovely American lady offered to take a picture of me and Sarah in front of the canyon and proceeded to say that we were the first English speaking people they had come across for hours. Everyone else seemed to be European.
&lt;a title="IMGP0402 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5895649595/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5279/5895649595_50e1067e89.jpg" alt="IMGP0402" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
Stayed at Mather campground, really nice, in one of the main loops with good access to water and the toilets. (Aspen Loop, No. 21). Now was the time to set up the tent. Luckily we had a trial run of putting the tent up from the comfort of my back garden. All went pretty smoothly and within 15mins we were in our sauna of a tent. We then chilled out and set up camp properly (got water, had a a beer etc) whilst making plans for the next day. Then we went to Hopi point to watch the sunset, was absolutely stunning and we took a tonne of photos.
&lt;a href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5896220954/" title="IMGP0426 by jonfry22, on Flickr">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6019/5896220954_f9ab134f23.jpg" width="500" height="375" alt="IMGP0426">&lt;/a>
The most American part of the trip was when the sun set and everyone started clapping, classic. We caught the shuttle bus back to camp and was pretty much pitch black by the time we got back, went to sleep about 9pm excited for a proper walk around the canyon tomorrow.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As always check Flickr for &lt;del>all&lt;/del> most of the pictures.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 5 - route 66, flagstaff, hollister</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-5-route-66-flagstaff-hollister/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2011 11:56:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-5-route-66-flagstaff-hollister/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today was a more leisurely day. We woke up at 8ish and slobbed until around 10, eating pop-tarts in bed. Opened the curtains to see a hummingbird inches from my face, Sarah was jealous. We packed up and checked out around 11 to hit the road. Not as long a drive as yesterday, approx 240miles. We crossed the Colorado river and entered our 3rd state – Arizona. Sarah was map reading so missed the welcome to Arizona sign lol.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We took the wrong exit off the interstate and it just so happened to be a truck inspection lane, where they weigh and inspect the goods. We queued with the trucks until we got to the weighing scales and luckily there was a woman in the window. We played the touristy card and said ‘uhh we took the wrong exit.. how do we get to route 66?? Sorry!’. No doubt a funny sight for all the truck drivers that day.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We stopped off at Walmart in Kingman. It was a huge super-center – bigger than anything in the UK. Wandered round for like 45mins, picking up yet more American junk food (so cheap! 1ltr powerade was 80cents) and filled up the cooler. Then we got on to Route 66 and began the famous drive, wow fantastic views pretty much the whole way.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="wp-caption alignnone" style="width: 510px;">&lt;a title="IMGP0317 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5886258849/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5156/5886258849_119dd32456.jpg" alt="IMGP0317" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
&lt;p class="wp-caption-text">Road As Far As The Eye Can See&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
Awkwardly stuck behind a Volkswagen for a while, dithering whether to overtake (we did). Saw loads of tumbleweed but was all too quick to take a photo of. Stopped at a gimmicky shop but didn’t buy anything. It’s a shame route 66 is looking quite run down, but it looks like it’s supposed to be that way.
&lt;div class="wp-caption alignnone" style="width: 510px;">&lt;a title="IMGP0332 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5886825392/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5271/5886825392_e5a299be20.jpg" alt="IMGP0332" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
&lt;p class="wp-caption-text">Route 66&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
We hopped back on the freeway at Seligman heading deeper into Arizona. When all of a sudden the landscape changed into forest country. There were warnings for elk and deer. We saw a deer woohoo… shame it was dead on the side of the road. We reached a max altitude of 7500ft and the temps started dropping to a lovely 85.
&lt;p>On to Flagstaff, where we hadn’t pre-booked a motel so pulled into the ‘budget host inn’ on route 66. The Asian guy hardly spoke English and was like ‘you eat? eat?’ whilst taking a bite out of an imaginary sandwich. He was recommending a place for us to go for dinner. After checking in we went for a drive. We ended up at the Flagstaff Mall and Marketplace – where dreams come true. We made a B-line for the Hollister store, and spent the next hour inside splurging $200 on 15 items of clothing. Everything was on sale, with a sale on the sale stuff of 50% (if that makes sense). Sarah bought a t-shirt for just $4.50!&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="wp-caption alignnone" style="width: 385px;">&lt;a title="IMGP0349 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5886824908/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5303/5886824908_13680d5330.jpg" alt="IMGP0349" width="375" height="500" />&lt;/a>
&lt;p class="wp-caption-text">Hollister Tags&lt;/p>
&lt;/div>
After returning to the checkout 3 times we thought we better leave before we started to look weird. We headed to Del Taco, and yes you guessed it – we got a taco. It was good, filling food.
&lt;p>Back to the motel now, with a chair propped up against the door. A nervous nights sleep ahead, not helped by CBS warning of monsoons coming this weekend…Grand Canyon tomorrow so may not be on till 1st July when we’ll probably be in Page, AZ.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 4 - on the road</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-4-on-the-road/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2011 11:47:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-4-on-the-road/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today we were up early, as we would be doing our longest drive of the trip. So we had some pop-tarts, and packed all our stuff in to the car and headed off. As we left about 3 fire trucks drove past and as we pulled out just down the road from our hotel there was a building on fire. We pulled into our first gas station and tried to do pay at pump using credit card, but it was asking for a zip code (using only numbers) so had to go in and pay cash. We didn&amp;rsquo;t have a clue how much, as you have to pay before you pump, so we paid $40 but it only came to $20 for half a tank!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We then were onto the interstate and pulled  off along the way to Fry&amp;rsquo;s Electronics. We were looking to buy a kindle, but unfortunately they didn&amp;rsquo;t sell any. Jon nearly wet himself from excitement when we were there because A. It was called Fry&amp;rsquo;s electronics and B. It&amp;rsquo;s just about the coolest computer shop in the world. We decided to head to walmart - and here we bought a kindle! It cost $114 and the case was $35. It&amp;rsquo;s awesome and have put on some guidebooks with maps which shall be helpful.
&lt;a title="IMGP0187 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883119981/">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6019/5883119981_c010b10524.jpg" alt="IMGP0187" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>
As we carried onwards the temperature started going up, we were also going up as we were about 3000ft up and it was 100 degrees. We got to palm desert, and were using google directions which unfortunately got us lost and we ended up doing a bit of backtracking till we found the interstate. Along this road were signs advising us to turn off the air con, which we did as we were worried so we had the windows wide open. We pulled off into Joshua Tree NP, our first national park! We drove around and stopped at Cholla Cactus Garden and a few other viewpoints to take some pics, but we were both pretty hot so didn&amp;rsquo;t get out of the car much. The Joshua Trees were really cool and the scenery was gorgeous.
&lt;a title="IMGP0219 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883122023/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5195/5883122023_432a13872a.jpg" alt="IMGP0219" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We then continued to drive on single lane roads, where we didn&amp;rsquo;t see any cars for miles and were just surrounded by desert. Every now and then we&amp;rsquo;d pass some shacks and trailers, and big clumps of mailboxes on the side of the road. It was now 115 degrees so we didn&amp;rsquo;t get out of the car and kept the air con on. We passed salt flats and really long freight trains, and came close to hitting some chipmunks.
&lt;a title="IMGP0268 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883697226/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5269/5883697226_19a5d52fab.jpg" alt="IMGP0268" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We were getting low on fuel but thought we should be fine as we had approx 100miles to do with 150 in the tank. We got a bit worried when the light came on, but then we passed the &amp;lsquo;Welcome to Nevada - The Silver State&amp;rsquo; sign and we only had 5 miles left to drive. We passed a tree full of eagles which was pretty cool, before we headed into our hotel. For £14 a night this place is a bargain, we even had a free upgrade! Tomorrow we will be entering Arizona and driving Route 66!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 3 - Sightseeing in san diego</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-3-sightseeing-in-san-diego/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2011 11:46:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-3-sightseeing-in-san-diego/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today we had an eventful day &amp;ldquo;well&amp;rdquo; planned out and we were super excited. It was going to be our first proper day of sight seeing. Sarah was awake at 0620 and couldn&amp;rsquo;t get back to sleep so was an early start. We got up showered and ready, had chocolate fudge pop-tarts for breakfast filled up all our bottles of water and set off!
First we went to Cabrillo national monument which was an easy drive, really nice and went past some very nice houses. We met our first Ranger who we bought our America the Beautiful pass off, which was $80 and is entry to all the National Parks/Monuments. We parked up and headed to the view point where there were views overlooking the Navy airbase San Diego, views were great and you could even see Mexico in the distance. The airbase is one of the busiest in the U.S and while we were standing there we saw a Jet, a few helicopters, loads of normal planes and two navy destroyers.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0039 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883652262/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5143/5883652262_bbb5b5c58c.jpg" alt="IMGP0039" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a> Me at Viewpoint[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Then we drove down to the tidepools and sat watching the surfers surf whilst eating some Cheetos.
Moving on, we then went to Old town which is titled the birth place of California. Getting there was quite a problem, we drove round in what seemed like circles, nearly got run over by a train (dodgy crossings) and struggled to find somewhere to park. Was worth all the hassle of getting there though as it really felt like we were in Mehico when we were there. There was live music being played by a cool group of Mexicans, and the food smelt lovely.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0099 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883102215/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5151/5883102215_e69499a3b1.jpg" alt="IMGP0099" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a> Sarah at Fiesta de Reyes[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Dashed off to Balboa park which is the U.S&amp;rsquo;s largest urban park. It was full of museums and a few nice gardens. Coolest thing about it though was the &amp;ldquo;designated dog walking area&amp;rdquo; which looked like a scene from a Disney movie. Dogs running about with each other lol.
Now to Walmart where we did our main shop for our camping supplies. The area wasn&amp;rsquo;t great, from the walk from the car to best buy there was a crazy lady with a trolley talking to herself who I thought was gonna attack Sarah. Then the walk from best buy to Walmart a guy wanted to shake my hand but he looked like a crazy drug addict so we said No thanks and walked off.
We were quite glad to be leaving that area and heading to the Coronado bridge. Its one of the top 3 suicide bridge in the U.S after the golden gate bridge. Driving over it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too fun, roads felt tight and the locals seemed to totally ignore the speed limit and gun past us at 80 when the limit was 55. Got some good pics though and a cool video (will try to upload at some point, its 720p though so its huge).
We went to Coronado beach with the Hotel Del Coronado. Was an awesome hotel, right over the beach and was huge! Truly American beach with volleyball and surfers. Stayed here for a while and put our feet in the pacific ocean for the first time. Even though the air temp was 35, the sea was ICE cold.
At this point we were knackered so we headed back to the motel to crash out for an hour. Got hungry so we headed out to the&lt;span style="color: #000000;"> &lt;del datetime="2011-06-29T16:32:55+00:00">Jack Bauer&lt;/del> &lt;/span>&lt;a title="Karl Strauss" href="http://www.karlstrauss.com/index2.html" target="_blank">Karl Strauss &lt;/a>bar and grill/ microbrewery. Was a lovely place would definitely recommend. We both ordered a no frills cheeseburger. Sarah got a Karl Strauss amber larger, and I had a Scott Tiger&amp;rsquo;s IPL or IPA I don&amp;rsquo;t remember but it was good beer and won a world lager competition. Yeehar!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;375&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0182 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5883683072/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5063/5883683072_557c2d3d52.jpg" alt="IMGP0182" width="375" height="500" />&lt;/a> Me reading Sarah&amp;rsquo;s mind[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Tomorrow: 400mile drive through the desert..&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Day 2</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jun 2011 11:45:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/day-2/</guid><description>&lt;p>Good morning Los Angeles! Woke up today at 7.30am after a good catch up of sleep. First thing to do was shower, so off I went and after about 10mins I gave up. We could not work out how to turn it on. We searched everywhere for a way to turn it on. But nothing, so I had to wash in the sink. We had complimentary breakfast which was nice. Bagels and cinnamon swirls things. At 10am we had a free shuttle lift to Alamo where we picked up the car nice and easily. We were told to choose a compact car out of a selection, and could see lots of Chevrolet&amp;rsquo;s but Jon spotted a one and only ford focus and was quick to say this was the one. So we jumped in and set off. As soon as we pulled out we spotted our first odd sight - a hobo with a trolley dancing in the middle of the road!!
[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Dancing Hobo&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0291 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5875440800/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5235/5875440800_98dd242f84.jpg" alt="IMGP0291" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>[/caption]
So I snapped a photo, and we managed to get on the freeway pretty easily with no problems. Jon was quite nervous to start but soon got used to it, and now wants an automatic lol.
 
We drove through Long Beach and the OC (Laguna, Newport and Huntington Beaches). All nice scenery with lots of surfers and expensive looking cars.
[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Corvette Stingray&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0316 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5876210910/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5111/5876210910_841f175011.jpg" alt="IMGP0316" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We got to our motel in downtown San Diego at approximately 3pm, and were quick to have a glass of water as we hadn&amp;rsquo;t drunk since that morning. After a little lie down, we decided to head downtown to Horton Plaza. We went to A&amp;amp;F but was a bit too expensive, so we went for a walk down 1st St. We ended up at the convention center and then the lively Gaslamp Quarter, where there were lots of bars and restaurants. A bit further up were a few shops where we made a few purchases - Jon a t-shirt and I got a vest. We bought some Mountain Dew and Cheetos as we walked back to the motel. I put some pics on the laptop and we paid $3 for wifi.
 
We then made some plans for tomorrow before we headed out at around 8pm to Mission Beach.
[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Mission Beach&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0004 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5875647527/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5065/5875647527_1ba5f58ca5.jpg" alt="IMGP0004" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was very lively with loud music and lots of police everywhere. We went on to the beach and took some piccies, was quite cold though so we picked up 2 giant slices of pizza to take back to the motel. Such good timing as we got back at 8.50pm and the new season of True Blood was premiering on HBO at 9pm :D So we watched that whilst eating our pizza.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Recap of Day 1</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/recap-of-day-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2011 11:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/recap-of-day-1/</guid><description>&lt;p>There is way too much stuff for me to write in this 5 minutes I have spare to go into detail about our first day so ill try to summarize.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Funny things:  Heathrow airport, women asked what our relationship status was, I said couple, she asked if we were married i said no, she laughed. Then went and told all her colleagues her apparently hilarious story&amp;hellip;WEIRD.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;Plane Food&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0256 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5875426260/">&lt;img src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5275/5875426260_7ec4651039.jpg" alt="Plane Food" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our flight from Heathrow was delayed from 1005 to 1115. If we had just been flying to J.F.K this would have been a minor annoyance but seeing as we had a connecting flight within an hour and a half from landing this was not good. The actual flight to J.F.K from heathrow was nice, Sarah&amp;rsquo;s first time on a jumbo jet and first time going on a plane with screens. Was great watched a few movies and watched some TV shows they had. Overall just as good as I thought it would be.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[caption id=&amp;quot;&amp;quot; align=&amp;ldquo;alignnone&amp;rdquo; width=&amp;ldquo;500&amp;rdquo; caption=&amp;ldquo;View from the plane&amp;rdquo;]&lt;a title="IMGP0268 by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5874872007/">&lt;img src="http://farm7.static.flickr.com/6009/5874872007_37d08e07a8.jpg" alt="View from the plane" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>[/caption]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When we landed we had already missed our 1500 connecting flight to LAX.We picked up our luggage as usual, went through customs fine but as I walked through, heard a customs officer say &amp;lsquo;ill take her&amp;rsquo; point at sarah then lead her away and proceed to search through her whole bag. Sarah the terrorist&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Then had to wait a half hour or more to find out if we would be put on the next flight. They said we were booked in for the 1700 flight which wasnt too bad. Re-checked in our luggage, by this time there was a HUGE backlog of luggage waiitng to be put onto the conveyor belt(this would cause problems, more later..).
Had a nice 10 minute wait till boarding our flight to LAX, got to wander through JFK (pretty nice airport) and can now say we have been to New York for all of a few minutes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Run out of time to write anymore on what happened on day 1.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Quick tip of the day: Go to the toilet on the plane before you get food, the queue after is devastating.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The night before the flight</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/the-night-before-the-flight/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2011 11:42:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/the-night-before-the-flight/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just hopped into bed at 9pm&amp;hellip;No i&amp;rsquo;m not ill just trying to catch some sleep before waking up at 3.45am to catch our flight to L.A. So unbelievably excited not sure if i&amp;rsquo;ll sleep a wink.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Flight details for tomorrow:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(10:05) London Heathrow to New York JFK: KL9085&lt;/p>
&lt;p>(15:00) JFK to Los Angeles LAX: KL5114&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Can use a site such as &lt;a title="Flight Stats" href="http://www.flightstats.com/go/FlightTracker/flightTracker.do" target="_blank">Flight Stats&lt;/a> and enter &amp;lsquo;Delta&amp;rsquo; as the airline and the flight number is just the 4 digit number e.g. KL9085 flight number would be 9085. Quite a good website, get to see our plane fly across the map with current altitude and speed(around 600mph I think).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Enough jibber jabber, Off to bed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A year's worth of planning</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/a-years-worth-of-planning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 11:39:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/a-years-worth-of-planning/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a title="Travel Planning by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5863615538/">&lt;img class="alignnone" src="http://farm6.static.flickr.com/5261/5863615538_96d34c1b61.jpg" alt="Travel Planning" width="500" height="375" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Today we started to pack(when I say we I mean Sarah), and it&amp;rsquo;s nice to see so much planning finally coming together.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Absolutely tipping down at the moment in Wales so can&amp;rsquo;t wait to finally get on with the trip and to some lovely American weather.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Have been trying to cram as many famous American movies before we go so we can snap some great photos.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>The trip of a lifetime</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/the-trip-of-a-lifetime/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2011 11:35:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/the-trip-of-a-lifetime/</guid><description>&lt;p>Counting down the days till our flight leaves to L.A. (currently 4 days). We (me and Sarah) have been planning the trip for the past year and its exciting to see it all coming together.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Consists of : &lt;strong>10,912 &lt;/strong>miles flown, &lt;strong>3,500 &lt;/strong>miles driven, &lt;strong>132 &lt;/strong>gallons of fuel, &lt;strong>21 &lt;/strong>days, &lt;strong>4 &lt;/strong>states visited, &lt;strong>2 &lt;/strong>people, &lt;strong>1&lt;/strong> car.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a title="Map of USA by jonfry22, on Flickr" href="http://www.flickr.com/photos/jonfry22/5856233835/">&lt;img alt="Map of USA" src="http://farm3.static.flickr.com/2729/5856233835_91021812aa.jpg" width="500" height="368" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For all the details in full please check out the &lt;a title="Road Trip USA" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2011/07/23/road-trip-usa/">Road Trip USA page&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p>
&lt;p>J.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>