<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>drive on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/drive/</link><description>Recent content in drive on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 22:41:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/drive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Grasmere, Lake District</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/grasmere-lake-district/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 22:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/grasmere-lake-district/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/grasmere.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1774" alt="grasmere" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/grasmere.jpg" width="490" height="706" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On Thursday Jon and I drove down to the Lake District. We decided to break the journey from Edinburgh to Cardiff by staying overnight at Grasmere, and on Friday continuing on to Alton Towers and arriving in Cardiff in the evening. It was a 3hr drive to Grasmere and driving through the Lake District was gorgeous.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We booked the &lt;a href="http://www.yha.org.uk/hostel/grasmere-butharlyp-howe" target="_blank">Youth Hostel&lt;/a> on Monday, and the only one which had private rooms still available was the one in Grasmere. Grasmere is known as the place William Wordsworth lived, and apparently he described it as &amp;ldquo;the loveliest spot that man hath ever found&amp;rdquo;. The youth hostel was in this lovely converted Victorian mansion:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/YHA-grasmere.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1775" alt="YHA grasmere" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/YHA-grasmere.jpg" width="490" height="731" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was a great, cheap place to stay. We spotted 3 deer just outside the hostel and lots of rabbits running about. We went for a walk, and having done some research before heading out we decided upon the &lt;a href="http://where2walk.co.uk/lake_district/lake_discoveries/easedale-tarn-from-grasmere/" target="_blank">walk to Easedale Tarn&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/easedale.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1778" alt="easedale" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/easedale.jpg" width="490" height="1439" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It was a nice and easy walk, although it rained the whole time. I took a few too many photos of lambs along the first quarter of the route (they were so cute!), but as my legs started to get rather wet we sped up the hill along the waterfalls. The views were fantastic.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We reached Easedale Tarn, and there were just a few people about so it was nice and quiet. Wish we had waterproof trousers though! On the way back towards Grasmere the ground was very wet and muddy. There were stepping stones almost the whole way which helped a lot (luckily I had wellies on so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t too bad), but some parts it seemed we were walking in a stream!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/easedale-tarn.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1777" alt="easedale tarn" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/easedale-tarn.jpg" width="490" height="1270" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>By the time we got back to the youth hostel we were soaked through and we turned the heating up to full to start drying out our shoes and all of our clothes. Jon had a nap for an hour whilst I read a book, and before we knew it it was dinner time! Which meant we had missed having a look around the village shops. I really wanted to go to the &lt;a href="http://www.grasmeregingerbread.co.uk/" target="_blank">Grasmere Gingerbread Shop&lt;/a>, but a look from the outside had to do instead&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/grasmere-gingerbread.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1773" alt="grasmere gingerbread" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/grasmere-gingerbread.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We ate at a pub in Grasmere called The Lamb Inn which was yummy, and finished it off with apple crumble and ice-cream.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The next day we woke up early and headed down to Alton Towers. We were there from 10-5 and luckily it stayed dry the whole time. It was super quiet too, with the longest queue being 15mins. So fun!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/altontowers.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1776" alt="altontowers" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/altontowers.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I would love to do some more exploring of the Lake District, hopefully with a bit less rain next time though!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Drive Through Holyrood Park</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/drive-through-holyrood-park/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 17:45:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/drive-through-holyrood-park/</guid><description>&lt;p>Making the most of the sunshine again today. Oh we&amp;rsquo;d love to live somewhere that is sunny all the time&amp;hellip; Today we went for a little drive around Holyrood Park, along Queen&amp;rsquo;s Drive. It&amp;rsquo;s a great one-way road with views across the sea to East Lothian and across Edinburgh itself. There are pull outs along the road and we stopped off at Dunsapie Loch. If you&amp;rsquo;re walking up Arthur&amp;rsquo;s Seat this is probably the best place to park up and walk if you&amp;rsquo;re looking for the shortest/easiest route up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/holyrooddrive.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1124" title="holyrooddrive" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/holyrooddrive.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="1348" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[BTW my camera doesn&amp;rsquo;t like the sun much]&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We had a walk about, watched the swans and people passing by. We noticed the same cyclist go by us 4 times in a short space of time, and the loop is 3.3miles up and down, go him!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Now I&amp;rsquo;m home I think I shall make some &lt;a title="Philly with Cadbury Chocolate Cheesecakes" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/philly-with-cadbury-chocolate-cheesecakes/">cadbury philly cheesecakes&lt;/a> (as requested by Jon), watch some TV and think about what to do this week. We are off back to Cardiff next Thursday for 2 weeks - can&amp;rsquo;t wait!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We Bought A Car</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/we-bought-a-car/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jul 2012 17:32:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/we-bought-a-car/</guid><description>&lt;p>After a few weeks of umming and ahhing over whether to buy a car, today we went ahead and bought one! We&amp;rsquo;ve been nervous about getting one since we&amp;rsquo;ve had so many problems in the past and they&amp;rsquo;re so much money, even last night we went to bed kinda swayed to the &amp;lsquo;we won&amp;rsquo;t get one&amp;rsquo; side. But we realised that some of our best memories include a car, and driving about and roadtrips are something we both love.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/newcar.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1107" title="newcar" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/newcar.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="982" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We bought a Ford Puma, mainly for its reliability, and got this one in particular because it was a good deal and had good history and all that stuff. We bought a return train ticket and we were both so nervous, but ended up returning with the car! Exciting times.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We drove back and stopped off at &lt;a href="http://www.pentlandhills.org/" target="_blank">Pentland Hills Regional Park&lt;/a> for a little walk by Threipmuir Reservoir whilst the sun popped out of the rain clouds. This is why we chose to buy a car, to make little trips like this that make us smile.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>