<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>university on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/university/</link><description>Recent content in university on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 15:41:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/university/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Graduation</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/graduation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2013 15:41:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/graduation/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/grad.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1884" alt="grad" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/grad.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I graduated university on Friday with a first class mathematics degree. My 4 year student chapter is over. I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss my friends. I&amp;rsquo;m going to miss having a good timetable which may include a day off and lie-ins or early finishes. I might even miss the bus journeys and the study sessions in the library with frantic last minute revision. It&amp;rsquo;s been a fun 4 years, filled with so many good memories. All of the exams, midterms and projects caused a lot of stress at times, and sometimes I struggled with motivation to study day and night for the weeks leading up to the final exams. But it was so &lt;em>so&lt;/em> worth it.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/gradpics.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1885" alt="gradpics" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/gradpics.jpg" width="490" height="1693" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Finished.</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/finished/</link><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2013 19:22:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/finished/</guid><description>&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/uniwork.jpg">&lt;img class=" wp-image-1759 aligncenter" alt="uniwork" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/05/uniwork.jpg" width="314" height="461" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
On Friday I had my last ever exam at University. 4 years of studying are over and it's on to the big wide world now! Since I've finished I've been tidying and clearing out the flat, it gets so messy during revision times and I'm so happy to get rid of all of my notes that filled 8 lever arched files. I can now do fun things again - woohoo!!
&lt;p>Hope you are having a great bank holiday weekend :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Study Time: Final Round</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/study-time-final-round/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2013 22:07:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/study-time-final-round/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/04/study.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1638" alt="study" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/04/study.jpg" width="490" height="537" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Revision is now in full flow. I&amp;rsquo;ve submitted my dissertation (WOO!) and my last ever MATLAB coursework (YAY!), and now it&amp;rsquo;s just 3 exams to go and it&amp;rsquo;ll all be finished. Jon and I are celebrating completing our dissertations by going for a meal tomorrow to Jamie&amp;rsquo;s Italian (we have a free &lt;a href="https://www.jamieoliver.com/italian/signup" target="_blank">£10 voucher&lt;/a> to spend that comes with the card ;) ).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Scary but exciting that it&amp;rsquo;s almost over!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Study Time</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/study-time/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2012 18:17:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/study-time/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/IMGP4011.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1369" title="revision" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/IMGP4011.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">2 weeks today = my first exam of four...&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">4 weeks today = Christmas holidays begin!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">The countdown begins, and until then I shall drink lots of tea and eat lots of sugary snacks to keep me going through revision. These are my penultimate exams at university so I'm starting to stress, but I'm looking forward to getting them done and driving back home to Cardiff for Christmas :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Life Lately</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/life-lately/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2012 19:25:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/life-lately/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have finally finished 3rd year - yay! My final exam was on Monday so I&amp;rsquo;m done with uni for 4 whole months - summer has begun! But sadly the weather isn&amp;rsquo;t agreeing with me on that&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/hail.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-672" title="hail" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/hail.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="346" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Aside from the bad weather (it&amp;rsquo;s Britain after all) I&amp;rsquo;m enjoying not having to revise anymore and having time to catch up on tv, etc. This currently consists of HIMYM (ah season finale :o), Gossip Girl (another season finale!), Glee (yes I&amp;rsquo;m a fan), Game of Thrones (crazy), and I&amp;rsquo;ve started rewatching The Shield (watch it).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve also been busy with my scrapbook and managed to complete 3 pages yesterday. Any guesses at to where these photos were taken? ;) My &lt;strong>scrapbook peek #3&lt;/strong>:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/scrapbook-3.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-673" title="scrapbook 3" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/scrapbook-3.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="1019" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And finally I&amp;rsquo;ve put film in my &lt;a title="My New Diana F+ Camera" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/my-new-diana-f-camera/">new camera&lt;/a> and have started snapping away. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to get it developed even if they do turn out bad..&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/diana-viewfinder.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-674" title="diana viewfinder" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/diana-viewfinder.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="431" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So now I&amp;rsquo;ve got more time on my hands I shall be filling my moleskine up with things I want to do and ideas for the blog. Hopefully things will be getting ticked off a lot more frequently.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Oh and sorry about the amount of brackets used in this post, got a bit carried away!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time For a Catch Up</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/catch-up-time/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Apr 2012 18:20:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/catch-up-time/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve had a busy week the past week and thought it&amp;rsquo;s time to catch up with everything whilst I have some time before dinner and a movie night with Jon :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On Sunday we both volunteered at the &lt;a title="Rock ‘n’ Roll Edinburgh Half Marathon" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/rock-n-roll-edinburgh-half-marathon/">Rock &amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo; Roll Edinburgh Half Marathon&lt;/a>, which was really fun and it was such a nice sunny day. We were over at Holyrood park all morning and after holding rope for the corral starts we ate hotdogs before the runners started to come through the finish line with the female winner after 1hr 16mins! We were working at the chip retrieval where we clipped the chips off people shoes, yum. Was a great day, maybe some time we&amp;rsquo;ll be running it :p&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Afterwards we went to Usher Hall to see &lt;a href="http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b00lwxj1/features/banglive" target="_blank">Bang Goes the Theory Live&lt;/a> (not to be confused with the Big Bang Theory)! We managed to get free tickets and it was pretty good. Lots of kids though and I was sat by a boy who couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop jumping up and down in his seat so I was flinging around lol, that was quite annoying after a while&amp;hellip; Was an entertaining show though for all the family and educational too, and the audience were involved which the kids loved. It was my first time inside Usher Hall and it&amp;rsquo;s a really nice venue.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On Monday - Wednesday Jon had family up to visit which was lovely. It&amp;rsquo;s so good when we have visitors, sucks we are so far away! They were staying in an amazing apartment right in town with heated floors which were so nice and even a garden. Hate how cold our flat is :( There was this mirror in the lounge which I love:&lt;/p>
&lt;img class="aligncenter" title="mirror" src="http://media-cache2.pinterest.com/upload/26529085275208448_hmRtjSl6_f.jpg" alt="" width="465" height="309" />
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s made of magazine pages rolled up in to squares. So I had a look at how to make it and found lots of other things to make with magazine paper which &lt;a href="http://pinterest.com/sarahls12/craft-ideas/" target="_blank">I pinned on Pinterest&lt;/a> (so addictive!)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before Jon&amp;rsquo;s family had to leave back to Cardiff we had free cocktails at the &lt;a href="http://www.therutlandhotel.com/bar-rutland-hotel-2.htm" target="_blank">Rutland Hotel Bar&lt;/a> :D They were so good - in order of yummiest:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>42 Ways to Leave Your Lover&lt;/strong> &lt;em>- 42 Below Kiwi, Cointreau, mango juice, citrus and basil combine for a long cool thirst quencher.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Lemon and Lychee Caipiroska&lt;/strong> - &lt;em>Sharp and tangy with a hint of tropical sweetness, Absolut Citron and lychee juice combine for an exciting twist on a classic.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Crimson Kisses&lt;/strong> - &lt;em>A romantic blend of fresh raspberries, Bombay Sapphire, rose liqueur &amp;amp; sparkling rose wine.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>The Rutland Mai-Ta&lt;/strong> - &lt;em>Classic Mai-Tai recipe made with our Rutland rum blend, fresh lime and Grand Marnier.&lt;/em>&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
Would definitely go back there for more!
&lt;p>We also had a wander around the shops, and went to &lt;a href="http://www.anthropologie.eu/" target="_blank">Anthropologie&lt;/a> which I&amp;rsquo;d never been to before but Jon&amp;rsquo;s parents had been whilst in the US. It&amp;rsquo;s such a nice shop, pretty expensive, but they had a sale! Jon&amp;rsquo;s Mum found this plate and we had to get it, down to £3 from £12:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/purple-plate.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-554" title="purple plate" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/purple-plate.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="630" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So now they&amp;rsquo;ve gone back we are sad they&amp;rsquo;ve gone and we have to get back to studying. Revision plan has kicked back in and my first exam is this Tuesday&amp;hellip; :/ Starting to stress but thing like tea, cake and highlighters make it all a bit better.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/uni-work.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-555" title="uni work" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/uni-work.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="183" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So that&amp;rsquo;s my week so far. The rest will be a nice evening tonight then stuck at my desk trying to get all this revision in to my head. I shall be sleeping with symbols in my dreams.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>