<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cookies on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/cookies/</link><description>Recent content in cookies on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 22:10:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/cookies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Double Chocolate 'Millie's Cookies Style' Cookies</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/double-chocolate-millies-cookies-style-cookies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2013 22:10:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/double-chocolate-millies-cookies-style-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1959" alt="doublechoccookie" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This morning I baked these cookies and now there are only 2 leftover&amp;hellip; so I think that means they were a success! Double chocolate cookies are so good - the more chocolate the better. Especially when the cookies are chewy and soft and crisp on the outside.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I halved the recipe to make 10 so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t feel too guilty if they got eaten quickly (although now I wish I made more). So here&amp;rsquo;s the recipe below, which I advise you don&amp;rsquo;t halve ;)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie2.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1960" alt="doublechoccookie2" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie2.jpg" width="490" height="366" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;em>125g butter, melted//100g light brown soft sugar//125g caster sugar//1 egg//1 tsp vanilla extract//175g self-raising flour//50g cocoa powder//½ tsp salt//200g chocolate&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
Preheat the oven to 180°C/gas mark 4.
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Put the melted butter in a bowl (to melt it I microwave my butter in the bowl) and stir together with the brown sugar and caster sugar&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Combine with the egg and vanilla extract&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Add the flour, cocoa powder and salt and mix it all together until it becomes doughy&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>Chop up the chocolate (I use Dairy Milk) and mix it in to the cookie dough&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Divide the cookie dough in to 20 evenly sized pieces and place on to trays lined with baking paper. Place the trays in the oven for 7-8 minutes. The cookies may not look cooked but they will stiffen as they cool. You don&amp;rsquo;t want to overcook them if you like them chewy inside. Leave them to cool on a wire rack, and enjoy!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie3.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1958" alt="doublechoccookie3" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/doublechoccookie3.jpg" width="490" height="699" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Want more chewy cookies like this? Try these simple &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2012/05/31/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/" target="_blank">chocolate chip cookies&lt;/a>, lovely &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2013/06/01/fresh-mint-chocolate-cookies/" target="_blank">fresh mint chocolate cookies&lt;/a>, or these amazing &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2013/03/29/chewy-chocolate-toffee-waffle-cookies/" target="_blank">chocolate toffee waffle cookies&lt;/a>!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Fresh Mint Chocolate Cookies</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/fresh-mint-chocolate-cookies/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2013 17:32:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/fresh-mint-chocolate-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintchoccookie.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1810" alt="mintchoccookie" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintchoccookie.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I am back from my holiday to Poland (more on that to follow) and am enjoying the weekend with these cookies and watching movies before Jon starts his grad job on Monday!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I brought some fresh home grown mint back from Poland, thanks to Natalie&amp;rsquo;s mum, and decided to use it to make these cookies. Mint choc chip is one of my favourite flavours, and is usually my first choice when choosing ice-cream.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I followed my go-to &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2012/05/31/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/" target="_blank">Chewy ‘Millie’s Cookie Style’ Cookies recipe&lt;/a>, but replaced the 225g flourwith 185g self-raising flour and 40g cocoa powder. I added the chopped mint, which was around 2.5 tbsp, at the end along with 200g dark chocolate chips.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintcookiedough.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1811" alt="mintcookiedough" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintcookiedough.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The dough made 14 regular cookies and I used the left overs (which would make 6 regular cookies) to make a giant cookie which I baked in a cake tin. I flattened it down in the pan with my knuckles to speed up the cooking time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/bigmintcookiedough.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1812" alt="bigmintcookiedough" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/bigmintcookiedough.jpg" width="490" height="412" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Then cook for around 8mins, adding a couple more minutes for the larger one, and they&amp;rsquo;re done. They are super chewy and so tasty. I love the fresh taste of the mint with the dark chocolate, half of them have already been eaten..&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintcookie.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1813" alt="mintcookie" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/mintcookie.jpg" width="490" height="1009" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chewy Chocolate Toffee Waffle Cookies</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/chewy-chocolate-toffee-waffle-cookies/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2013 23:32:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/chewy-chocolate-toffee-waffle-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cwcookie.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1610" alt="cwcookie" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cwcookie.jpg" width="490" height="360" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I thank Jon for these cookies. We went to Lidl yesterday to grab some pizza, and whenever we&amp;rsquo;re in Lidl a pack of toffee waffles (also called caramel wafers) always seem to end up in our shopping. They are so good and the added cinnamon flavour in these ones make them even better.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cw.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1608" alt="cw" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cw.jpg" width="490" height="343" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So I&amp;rsquo;ve been wanting to make chocolate and toffee cookies for a while now, and Jon suggested using the toffee waffles. Today I made them, and oh are they good! They are sooo chewy and I love how the caramel oozes out from the waffles, and with the dairy milk, well they&amp;rsquo;re certainly full of sugar! I halved my &lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2012/05/31/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/" target="_blank">Chewy ‘Millie’s Cookie Style’ Cookies recipe&lt;/a> to make the cookie dough, and used 2 broken up waffles and around 15 blocks of dairy milk (I cut each block in half), and managed to make 12 cookies.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cwcookie2.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1609" alt="cwcookie2" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/03/cwcookie2.jpg" width="490" height="710" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They are seriously good warm when they&amp;rsquo;re still a bit gooey&amp;hellip; Enjoy!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Life Lately</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/life-lately-3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2012 15:39:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/life-lately-3/</guid><description>&lt;p>So I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write a catch up post as it&amp;rsquo;s been a while. It&amp;rsquo;s now a month till exams and it&amp;rsquo;s starting to really sink in that by April uni will be over, forever. So I&amp;rsquo;m making sure I make the most of it and come out with a good degree, which means most of my time is taken up with studying.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I try to keep one weekend day mostly free of work, and today is one of those days :) This morning Jon and I went to the cinema to see a screening of &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1024648/" target="_blank">Argo&lt;/a> which was really good (and I&amp;rsquo;d recommend it), followed by some food shopping and some online catch-up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s a few things I&amp;rsquo;ve been up to recently&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/cows.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1351" title="cows" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/cows.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="656" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We went for a walk in the Pentlands with some friends when the sun came out. It was so muddy and we went the steepest possible way up the hill. The way down was particularly funny when everyone slipped in the mud except for me ha! But we do really need to invest in some walking boots :p We also stumbled across this gathering of highland cattle which completely blocked our path, so we patiently waited for them to move as we were too scared to get close!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/rolocookies.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1352" title="rolocookies" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/rolocookies.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I baked &lt;a title="Chewy ‘Millie’s Cookie Style’ Cookies" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/" target="_blank">cookies&lt;/a>, rolo ones, that lasted 2 days at most.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/halloween.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1353" title="halloween" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/halloween.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="326" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I went to a Halloween party as a skeleton! The pic on the left was taken a couple of days before the party when I did a trial run of the make-up so it&amp;rsquo;s a bit rough. Was a great party and I only spent £2 on my &amp;lsquo;costume&amp;rsquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/sparklers.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1354" title="sparklers" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/11/sparklers.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="150" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And finally today I picked up some &lt;a href="http://www.tesco.com/free-sparklers/free-sparklers.pdf" target="_blank">free sparklers&lt;/a> from Tesco (click the link to get the coupon), a few of us plan on going up Blackford Hill to watch some fireworks tomorrow night, can&amp;rsquo;t wait!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That&amp;rsquo;s all for now, I&amp;rsquo;m going to put on the kettle for a hot chocolate and try to apply for some jobs. Have a nice Sunday!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Lost Cookies</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/lost-cookies/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2012 16:26:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/lost-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>I am a big &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0411008/" target="_blank">Lost&lt;/a> fan. When it was on TV (over 2 years ago it finished!) me and Jon were both hooked. And I admit I was a bit overly hooked; I was on the forums speculating theories and all. I know sometimes it did go a bit crazy and there were so many questions to be answered, but it was the characters that I loved about it. It&amp;rsquo;s one of my favourite TV shows along with The Shield, and the reasons for both are because of the characters and how much I cared about them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So now we&amp;rsquo;ve just started to watch it all over again! I baked some cookies using my &lt;a title="Chewy ‘Millie’s Cookie Style’ Cookies" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/">go-to recipe&lt;/a>, and decided to quickly ice some of them with a Lost theme. Yep one had the numbers on, and another with the dharma logo. Too cool ha.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/lostcookie.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1018" title="lostcookie" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/lostcookie.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They were as yummy as ever, and we pretty much ate them all whilst watching 5 episodes of the show. Although I think we got through most of them in the first episode&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Were you a Lost fan? Love/Hate the ending?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Chewy 'Millie's Cookie Style' Cookies</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 May 2012 14:39:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/chewy-millies-cookie-style-cookies/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/cookies.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-787" title="cookies" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/cookies.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="438" />&lt;/a>
I&amp;rsquo;ve just finished making these cookies and they are soo good! I&amp;rsquo;ve only made cookies a couple of times before and usually am disappointed. So this time I searched on blogs looking for a Millie&amp;rsquo;s Cookie style cookie (yummy) and stumbled upon &lt;a href="http://laureneasmith.blogspot.co.uk/2008/05/millies-cookie-recipe.html" target="_blank">this&lt;/a>. And I&amp;rsquo;m so glad I did.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>These cookies are amazing, crispy on the outside and chewy in the middle - just how I like them. Jon gave them a definite thumbs up too, and so this will be my go-to recipe for cookies now. I went for simple milk choc chip cookies using a bar of dairy milk and a flake. Can&amp;rsquo;t wait to experiment with different flavours in the future!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So here&amp;rsquo;s how they were made, thanks to &lt;a href="http://laureneasmith.blogspot.co.uk/2008/05/millies-cookie-recipe.html" target="_blank">this blog&lt;/a> which I adapted a little as I went.&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/baking-cookies1.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-782" title="baking cookies1" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/baking-cookies1.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="1467" />&lt;/a>&lt;em>125g butter, softened//100g light brown soft sugar//125g caster sugar//1 egg//1 tsp vanilla extract//225g self-raising flour//½ tsp salt//1 small bar dairy milk and 1 flake&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">Firstly preheat the oven to 180°C, gas mark 4.&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">1. Put the brown and caster sugar in a bowl and cream together with the butter (I melted half of it to speed up the process)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">2. Combine with the egg and the vanilla extract&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">3. Add the flour and salt and mix it all together so it becomes doughy&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">4. Chop up the dairy milk and crumble the flake and mix everything together&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">Finally roll the dough into a big sausage shape and cut it into 20 pieces and place on 2 trays lined with baking paper. As I didn't have large enough baking trays I could only fit 14 cookies on so with the rest I made one big cookie in a round cake tin. They go in the oven for 7mins, although they may not look cooked they should be so take them out to cool. The outside should stiffen and crisp as they cool. Or you can cook them for a bit longer if you prefer! (For me 8mins was perfect with my oven and preference)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">And enjoy! I sure did ;)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/IMGP3004.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-789" title="IMGP3004" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/05/IMGP3004.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="151" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">I think the big cookie would be great iced as a birthday cookie, just like at Millie's cookies!&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">S. xo&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>