<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/home/</link><description>Recent content in home on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 20:57:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Luckies Scratch Map</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/luckies-scratch-map/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2014 20:57:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/luckies-scratch-map/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jul/IMG_1822-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Scratch Map1"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I bought this Luckies scratch map (from &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/exec/obidos/ASIN/B003NCIPS6/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Amazon&lt;/a>) a couple of weeks ago and I love it. I&amp;rsquo;ve only scratched off the countries that Jon and I have been to together. (I didn&amp;rsquo;t scratch Alaska/Hawaii as part of the USA though and decided to treat those seperately.) We need to go to more countries so I can scratch them off as it&amp;rsquo;s looking pretty unscratched!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I framed it in an &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.ikea.com/gb/en/catalog/products/00128409/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>IKEA Ribba frame&lt;/a> (the one that has a 15 photo mount) which was almost perfect size - I just had to trim down some of the width to fit. Now I need to get it up on the wall and make some plans!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jul/IMG_1708-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Scratch Map2"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>8 months</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/8-months/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2014 16:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/8-months/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1046.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months1"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Jon and I have been in this flat in Edinburgh for just over 8 months now. And we love it! The high ceilings and big windows are my favourite and there&amp;rsquo;s so much space (we even have some empty cupboards/drawers still!).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1550.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months2"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I realised looking through these photos that I must have a thing for plants or I just like to take photos of them. The olive tree in our kitchen is my favourite of all. It&amp;rsquo;s from IKEA and it&amp;rsquo;s growing pretty fast with all the sunshine we&amp;rsquo;ve had lately.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here are a few photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken recently from around our home.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1549.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months3"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1548.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months4"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1542.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months5"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1070.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months6"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_1515.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months7"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Jun/IMG_0977.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="8months8"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Ampersand Cross Stitch</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/ampersand-cross-stitch/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2013 14:16:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/ampersand-cross-stitch/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-cross-stitch.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2025" alt="ampersand cross stitch" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-cross-stitch.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After finishing my &lt;a title="Breaking Bad Cross Stitch" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2013/09/10/breaking-bad-cross-stitch/" target="_blank">Breaking Bad cross stitch&lt;/a>, I really wanted to make another one and since I had leftover supplies I dove straight in. (I actually finished this cross stitch during Summer over a couple of days - it&amp;rsquo;s taken me this long to get a hoop to frame it!). I was looking for something simple to sew and after searching pinterest decided on a curly ampersand.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-plan.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2023" alt="ampersand plan" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-plan.jpg" width="490" height="580" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After drawing out the plan on grid paper I got sewing and couldn&amp;rsquo;t stop till it was finished! Very addictive. I really liked how it came out but was unsure how to frame it. Which brings me to this weekend when I finally decided to go and buy an 8&amp;quot; hoop. I painted it black for contrast (this was actually Jon&amp;rsquo;s idea!) and it can now be displayed, finally&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-cross-stitch-2.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-2024" alt="ampersand cross stitch (2)" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/11/ampersand-cross-stitch-2.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Breaking Bad Cross Stitch</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/breaking-bad-cross-stitch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2013 14:07:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/breaking-bad-cross-stitch/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/IMGP4632-001.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1981" alt="IMGP4632-001" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/09/IMGP4632-001.jpg" width="490" height="593" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I start my new full-time job next Tuesday, and whilst I&amp;rsquo;m not working I&amp;rsquo;ve been filling my weekdays with baking, crafting and housework. And watching back to back episodes of Grey&amp;rsquo;s Anatomy (addicted). Last week I decided to give cross stitching a go. It&amp;rsquo;s cheap and time-consuming and I can watch as much TV as possible whilst doing it. I haven&amp;rsquo;t cross stitched since I was 15 but it&amp;rsquo;s super simple to pick up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I had a browse on Etsy and decided to purchase this &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/uk/listing/125818162/breaking-bad-cross-stitch-pattern" target="_blank">Breaking Bad cross stitch&lt;/a> pattern. Breaking Bad is an awesome TV show from beginning to end (OK we are a couple episodes from the end but we know it&amp;rsquo;s gonna be crazy good) so I thought it&amp;rsquo;d be cool to remember it with this cross stitch. Jon gave it a thumbs up too which sealed the deal. I bought all the supplies online and got started on it as soon as it was all delivered.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I really enjoyed making it and I&amp;rsquo;ve already begun my next cross stitch project. Think I&amp;rsquo;ve found a new hobby here..&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DIY Black&amp;White Geometric Cushion</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/diy-blackwhite-geometric-cushion/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2013 21:00:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/diy-blackwhite-geometric-cushion/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/diybwcushion.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1920" alt="diybwcushion" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/diybwcushion.jpg" width="490" height="183" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This was a cushion cover DIY that I made before dinner this evening. Super quick and easy. I had found a couple plain white linen covers that I bought off eBay a while ago and decided to jazz one up a bit with a geometric pattern. It&amp;rsquo;s got hexagons, triangles, circles, squares and probably some more shapes thrown in!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcushionsteps.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1919" alt="bwcushionsteps" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcushionsteps.jpg" width="490" height="550" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I drew out the lines first using a pencil and ruler starting with a cross through the middle. I didn&amp;rsquo;t do any measurements and just went with it. The good thing with cushion covers is they don&amp;rsquo;t have to be perfect because when they are filled they&amp;rsquo;ll be all bendy anway and you won&amp;rsquo;t see if the lines are a bit off.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I used my &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Sharpie-Rub-a-Dub%C3%82%C2%AE-Laundry-Marker-Black/dp/B00387BTJS/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1333231606&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank">Sharpie Laundry Marker&lt;/a> to draw over the lines (and placed cardboard inside the cover so it doesn&amp;rsquo;t transfer to the back), and then drew on the circles using buttons as stencils.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcusion1.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1922" alt="bwcushion1" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcusion1.jpg" width="490" height="1128" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It reminds me a bit of those ball and stick models from chemistry classes. I like how the pattern came out, and for just a half hour DIY it&amp;rsquo;s great!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcushion2.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1923" alt="bwcushion2" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/07/bwcushion2.jpg" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Freshen Up</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/freshen-up/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2013 15:15:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/freshen-up/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/plants.jpg">&lt;img class="alignnone size-full wp-image-1845" alt="plants" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2013/06/plants.jpg" width="490" height="1019" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The past 4 days I&amp;rsquo;ve spent spring cleaning the flat. I&amp;rsquo;ve cleared out so much stuff and made a little money selling a few things. I&amp;rsquo;ve rearranged the bedroom furniture and switched around shelving in the kitchen cupboards. It&amp;rsquo;s kept me busy whilst Jon&amp;rsquo;s been working, and since we are planning to move soon I figured it&amp;rsquo;d be a good time to get it done.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I love the fresh feeling from decluttering. I bought a couple things to replace some old stuff too which is always fun to do! Jon sleeps better now that we have lovely new pillows which we picked out from TK Maxx. We spent 15 minutes in the shop opening bags and feeling each pillow before we decided which ones to buy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I bought that aloe vera plant above from &lt;a href="http://www.ikea.com/gb/en/catalog/products/60234647/" target="_blank">IKEA&lt;/a> to replace my cactus that died over winter (I left it by the window and I think it froze to death). It&amp;rsquo;s so cool that you can break off a tip and use the gel on burns (it&amp;rsquo;s even edible apparently!) and it&amp;rsquo;s super easy to care for.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I also planted those seedlings above 4 days ago and they shot up after just a day. They are organic phacelia seeds that I ordered for free from &lt;a href="http://www.soilassociation.org/supportus/keepbritainbuzzing" target="_blank">Keep Britain Buzzing&lt;/a>. I scattered over just a few of the seeds from the packet but I still overdid it! Bees go crazy for these plants, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to move it outdoors at some point. If our next place doesn&amp;rsquo;t have a garden I may just have to find somewhere to scatter the rest of the seeds&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hope you are having a great Friday!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>7 ♥</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/7-e299a5/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Dec 2012 15:45:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/7-e299a5/</guid><description>&lt;p>Firstly, I just have to say EXAMS ARE OVER! I had my last exam today and it went really well. I&amp;rsquo;m so relieved to finish studying and know that all my hard work will hopefully pay off.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>So yesterday was mine and Jon&amp;rsquo;s 7 years-of-being-a-couple anniversary. We&amp;rsquo;re celebrating this weekend by cooking a yummy meal together and allowing ourselves to put the electric heating on ha!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I just wanted to share a couple things that I gave Jon, starting with his card and wrap:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4040.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1384" alt="cardwrap" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4040.jpg" width="490" height="243" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Love &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/61963605/love-is-exponential-letterpress-card?ref=sr_gallery_9&amp;amp;ga_search_query=cards+love&amp;amp;ga_order=most_relevant&amp;amp;ga_view_type=gallery&amp;amp;ga_ship_to=GB&amp;amp;ga_page=2&amp;amp;ga_search_type=handmade&amp;amp;ga_facet=handmade/paper_goods/cards/letterpresscards+love" target="_blank">this card&lt;/a>, it&amp;rsquo;s cute + math related = yay! It&amp;rsquo;s from &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/FatBunnyPress?ref=seller_info" target="_blank">FatBunnyPress on Etsy&lt;/a> - totally recommended. Also that pacman wrapping paper is just printable paper from &lt;a href="http://www.minieco.co.uk/halloween-printable-wrap/" target="_blank">Minieco&lt;/a> which is free. The site has lots of printable wraps and other cool templates; I want to try making these &lt;a href="http://www.minieco.co.uk/paper-gems/" target="_blank">paper gems&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="http://www.minieco.co.uk/3d-paper-diamonds/" target="_blank">diamonds&lt;/a>. Jon gave me origami paper too so they will be getting made!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4042.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1390" alt="book" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4042.jpg" width="490" height="243" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I had a 7x7&amp;quot; book made from &lt;a href="http://www.blurb.co.uk/" target="_blank">Blurb&lt;/a> of our time in Edinburgh as students. I&amp;rsquo;m so impressed by the quality. I used Bookify to put it all together, just dragged the pics in and played around with the pre-made page layouts, so easy! I think it looks great, and it&amp;rsquo;s something we&amp;rsquo;ll look back on and laugh at (there are a lot of embarrassing photos in there). The majority of pages are made up of photo grids (2x2 and 3x3), and there&amp;rsquo;s 40pages in total. Here are some photos of a few pages, poor lighting doesn&amp;rsquo;t do them justice unfortunately.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4043.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1391" alt="photobook" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/12/IMGP4043.jpg" width="490" height="1135" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If you want a good quality photobook, I&amp;rsquo;d recommend &lt;a href="http://www.blurb.co.uk/" target="_blank">Blurb&lt;/a>. I found a 30% off code online too, so have a Google if you fancy getting one for yourselves or as a gift!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hope you have a lovely weekend :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p>
&lt;p>// To Jon: I want to say how thankful I am of you, for keeping me sane during studying and making me laugh hysterically over things like &amp;ldquo;trudagrapevin&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Ranjit says..&amp;rdquo;. This next years going to be full of changes, like where we&amp;rsquo;ll live and having graduate jobs (fingers crossed ha)&amp;hellip; but I am so excited to do it all with you! I love you so much xx p.s. can&amp;rsquo;t wait to fill up our huge book - I love it! //&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Thoughts on USA Scrapbook</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/thoughts-on-usa-scrapbook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2012 21:42:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/thoughts-on-usa-scrapbook/</guid><description>&lt;p>I enjoyed making this scrapbook a lot. It&amp;rsquo;s such a big book that I wasn&amp;rsquo;t sure I could finish it. But I&amp;rsquo;m glad I chose a big project to put together for my first scrapbook as I learnt lots along the way. I started from the beginning and went through page by page, I think the improvements can be seen as the book progresses.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/travel-scrapbook2.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1299" title="travel scrapbook" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/travel-scrapbook2.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="276" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I always had making a scrapbook of the trip in my mind, so I made sure to keep hold of all those little bits and pieces whilst travelling to include in the book. This included the usual things like leaflets, receipts, menus, tickets, napkins, wristbands, tags, as well as random stuff like a drink stirrer and paper hat. Cool to look back on and great fillers too!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/favouritepages.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1289" title="favouritepages" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/favouritepages.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="734" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The pages above are my favourites. I think it&amp;rsquo;s because of the colours and how the pages are filled without looking cluttered. I also like the circle cut of the middle page to keep the pages flowing together. Or maybe it&amp;rsquo;s just because they feature doughnuts and ice-cream&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/pocket1.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1292" title="pocket" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/10/pocket1.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="367" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are quite a few pockets in the book which I struggled with at the start. Towards the end I found what worked best for me, and this was cutting down half a page and using the scrap to make a pocket to stick back on to the half page. It seems to be the sturdiest and it&amp;rsquo;s a lot easier to turn the page. For the pocket above I painted it black and cut out a window which I then covered in acetate.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My next scrapbook I&amp;rsquo;m thinking of making is a minibook, perhaps 4x6 - a lot smaller and manageable that way!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p>
&lt;p>Supplies: Fancy Pants patterned paper (it&amp;rsquo;s the little things), American Crafts remarks stickers, Echo Park collection kit (for the record), Paperchase travel stickers, Freckled Fawn washi tape. I used a &lt;a href="http://www.paperchase.co.uk/invt/00333125/" target="_blank">Paperchase kraft scrapbook&lt;/a> as the base, and Dovecraft adhesive runners and a &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Pilot-Rollerball-Rubber-Retractable-0-5mm/dp/B0027IXR8K/ref=wl_it_dp_o_nS_nC?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;colid=366HG8GNNQRHA&amp;amp;coliid=I1LW4TNRBEVZRJ" target="_blank">Pilot G205 pen&lt;/a> throughout the book.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Herb Progress Wk6</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herb-progress-wk6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 16:10:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herb-progress-wk6/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/09/herbs6.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1189" title="herbs6" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/09/herbs6.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="640" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>They survived!! After 2 weeks away in Cardiff I came back to my flat to find my herbs hadn&amp;rsquo;t died. In fact, the soil from the chives and basil was still nice and moist. As you can see from the pics they aren&amp;rsquo;t looking too great though.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The parsley in particular has gone quite wild. I wish I thinned that out earlier on since it&amp;rsquo;s all knotted together now. Not really sure what to do with the chives either. The basil on the other hand is looking fine, I&amp;rsquo;m tempted to thin it down to just one plant (moving the far right big one in to the middle of the pot) but then I might end up with nothing left&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Herb Progress Wk3</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herb-progress-wk3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2012 16:29:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herb-progress-wk3/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/herbs31.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1165" title="herbs3" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/herbs31.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="595" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As you can see they&amp;rsquo;re all still alive and growing :) I thinned the basil and parsley down quite a lot, I felt bad doing it but they were so overcrowded (the parsley&amp;rsquo;s still a bit wild). The parsley was pretty difficult as it&amp;rsquo;s become quite tangled but I managed to thin out about half of the seedlings. And now they are all starting to grow their second set of &amp;rsquo;true leaves'.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m off down to Cardiff tomorrow morning for the next two weeks, yay! I hope the herbs don&amp;rsquo;t all die by the time I get back though&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Herbs Progress Wk2</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herbs-progress-wk2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2012 18:15:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/herbs-progress-wk2/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/herbs3.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1132" title="herbs3" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/08/herbs3.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="524" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Woah they&amp;rsquo;re growing quick! Especially the parsley, since &lt;a title="Seedlings" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/seedlings/">last week&lt;/a> there were only 3 measly seedlings there. The basil is starting to grow it&amp;rsquo;s first &amp;rsquo;true&amp;rsquo; leaves, which means I&amp;rsquo;ll have to thin them out soon - I&amp;rsquo;m scared it&amp;rsquo;ll result in them all dying though. Not really sure what to do with the chives either, any ideas? Tempted to just leave them grow but I don&amp;rsquo;t want them to kill each other?! Hmm we&amp;rsquo;ll see how they do for now!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Seedlings</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/seedlings/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2012 16:46:26 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/seedlings/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/IMGP3379.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1112" title="herbseedlings" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/IMGP3379.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="326" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Yay! Some little seedlings have appeared a week after planting my &lt;a title="Grow Your Own Herbs" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/grow-your-own-herbs/">Gardener&amp;rsquo;s World Seeds&lt;/a>. The basil came up first and can already see I&amp;rsquo;ll have to do quite a bit of thinning with those. Only 3 of my parsley seeds have sprouted, but that&amp;rsquo;s better than none! The chives were the slowest to sprout, but now there are quite a few seedlings and they&amp;rsquo;re growing up fast.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hopefully they&amp;rsquo;ll all keep on growing now&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Grow Your Own Herbs</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/grow-your-own-herbs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jul 2012 14:06:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/grow-your-own-herbs/</guid><description>&lt;p>Last week I had a free £10 voucher to spend on eBay&amp;rsquo;s Home and Garden category, and I bought an angled palette knife and a herb kit. So today my BBC Gardeners&amp;rsquo; World Herb Kit arrived. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to grow herbs on our windowsill for a while now, and getting the free voucher meant I could purchase some!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/herbkit.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1085" title="herbkit" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/herbkit.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="205" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The kit comes with Chive, Parsley and Basil seeds, compost, tray and these cool pots that you can write on with chalk. I sowed the seeds today and hopefully they will grow so we can use them. Fingers crossed.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/herbs.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-1086" title="herbs" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/07/herbs.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="634" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Will post up on their progress after a week or so!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Motivational Print Inspiration</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/motivational-print-inspiration/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2012 11:55:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/motivational-print-inspiration/</guid><description>&lt;p>So I&amp;rsquo;ve had a blank canvas hanging around that I&amp;rsquo;ve been struggling to decide what to do with. I&amp;rsquo;ve been looking around the internet for ideas and have decided I want to do something motivational and bright.&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">Here's some prints I've gathered as inspiration, they're all so pretty!&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.259847025.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-914" title="il_570xN.259847025" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.259847025-240x300.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="300" />&lt;/a>
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/78604700/dreamcatcher-print-the-dreamcatcher-no1" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/ParadaCreations?ref=seller_info">ParadaCreations&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-913" title="il_570xN.217219513" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.217219513-239x300.jpg" alt="" width="239" height="300" />
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/68111893/be-awesome-today-8x10-art-print" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/LuciusArt?ref=seller_info">LuciusArt&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.339346931.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-915" title="il_570xN.339346931" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.339346931-300x240.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="240" />&lt;/a>
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/100484874/lets-take-chances-8x10-original-modern" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/purpleteadesigns?ref=seller_info">purpleteadesigns&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.215192925.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-916" title="il_570xN.215192925" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.215192925-240x300.jpg" alt="" width="240" height="300" />&lt;/a>
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/67620818/motivational-art-print-poster-great-day" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/ParadaCreations?ref=seller_info">ParadaCreations&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.264465144.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-917" title="il_570xN.264465144" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.264465144-205x300.jpg" alt="" width="205" height="300" />&lt;/a>
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/75421272/the-morning-sun-abstract-print-8-x-10?ref=sr_gallery_4&amp;amp;sref=sr_3b8b4fd7cf26e96576087da824c8d0d4e5c64cb6e9046527cf303652f3eb8046_1340558666_14096565_motivation&amp;amp;ga_search_query=motivational+print&amp;amp;ga_order=most_relevant&amp;amp;ga_view_type=gallery&amp;amp;ga_ship_to=ZZ&amp;amp;ga_ref=auto1&amp;amp;ga_search_type=handmade" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/AeropagitaPrints?ref=seller_info">AeropagitaPrints&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.305935476.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-medium wp-image-919" title="il_570xN.305935476" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/06/il_570xN.305935476-300x264.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="264" />&lt;/a>
Source: &lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/listing/91330017/art-print-fortune-favors-the-brave?ref=sr_gallery_1&amp;amp;ga_search_query=fortune+favors+the+brave&amp;amp;ga_order=most_relevant&amp;amp;ga_view_type=gallery&amp;amp;ga_ship_to=ZZ&amp;amp;ga_ref=auto1&amp;amp;ga_search_type=handmade&amp;amp;ga_facet=handmadefortune+favors+the+brave" target="_blank">etsy&lt;/a> (&lt;a href="http://www.etsy.com/shop/smalltalkstudio?ref=seller_info">smalltalkstudio&lt;/a>)&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">&lt;span style="text-align: left;">S. xo&lt;/span>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>DIY Stencil Quote Cushion</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/diy-stencil-quote-cushion/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Apr 2012 14:04:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/diy-stencil-quote-cushion/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/IMGP2686-001.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-496" title="FInished Pillow" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/IMGP2686-001.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="346" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A little while ago I stumbled upon the blog &lt;a href="http://witandwhistle.com/2012/01/16/diy-stencil-pillow/" target="_blank">Wit &amp;amp; Whistle&lt;/a> when I was looking for crafty ideas. I love cushions and was looking for a way I could customise one myself, and fell in love with this one, such a great idea! I had to make it as luckily the instructions sounded pretty straightforward. Click the link above for the detailed instructions, they&amp;rsquo;re really good!!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The only problem I had was deciding on what to actually put on the cushion. I wanted quite a long quote that would cover the entire cover, and there were so many I wanted. But I finally decided on &lt;a href="http://www.goodreads.com/quotes/show/22842" target="_blank">this quote&lt;/a> - gotta love Dr Seuss! The supplies I used were:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Plain Cushion Cover (Bought mine from H&amp;amp;M &lt;a href="http://www.hm.com/gb/product/83390?article=83390-E#article=83390-A" target="_blank">here&lt;/a>)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A Fabric Marker (Purchased from Amazon &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Sharpie-Rub-a-Dub%C3%82%C2%AE-Laundry-Marker-Black/dp/B00387BTJS/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1333231606&amp;amp;sr=8-1" target="_blank">here&lt;/a>)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A Stencil (Again from Amazon &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Helix-Lettering-Stencil-10mm-H40891/dp/B00290IYS4/ref=sr_1_2?s=officeproduct&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1333231651&amp;amp;sr=1-2" target="_blank">here&lt;/a> - I used the 30mm one)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A pencil&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Some cardboard (for placing inside cover)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/diy-cushion.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-498" title="diy cushion" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/diy-cushion.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="1189" />&lt;/a>
&lt;p>Then I did a couple of calculations and measurements to work out how many lines to do and words/letters per line. I used tape to make a straight line each time I did a row so it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t get all wonky. It&amp;rsquo;s definitely worth using a pencil with the stencil before the pen to make sure the words all fit in, remember the pen is permanent! Then it&amp;rsquo;s just simply using the fabric marker to stencil in the letters and fill them in.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/IMGP2690.jpg">&lt;img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-500" title="IMGP2690" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/04/IMGP2690.jpg" alt="" width="490" height="405" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>And it&amp;rsquo;s done :) It did take me quite a while to do but that&amp;rsquo;s because I do usually take a while over things like this, but I enjoy doing it! Really pleased with how it came out - these cushions would make great gifts too!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>