<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>books on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/books/</link><description>Recent content in books on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 17:43:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Summer Reading</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/summer-reading/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2014 17:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/summer-reading/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Aug/IMG_2046-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="summer reading"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Fault-Our-Stars-John-Green/dp/0141345659/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>The Fault in our Stars&lt;/a> by John Green | I read this at the beginning of summer after hearing so much about it. It was a good quick read and it was sad. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t so keen on the movie though.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/The-Light-Between-Oceans-Stedman/dp/0552778478/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>The Light Between Oceans&lt;/a> by M L Stedman | I had to try not to tear up whilst reading the second half on a long train journey. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t something I would normally go for and although I felt parts of it went quite slow, I enjoyed it overall.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Gone-Girl-Gillian-Flynn/dp/0753827662/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Gone Girl&lt;/a> by Gillian Flynn | I read this in Tunisia and it was a thrilling page turner. I&amp;rsquo;m still not sure how I feel about the ending though.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/gp/product/000749145X/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>The Shock of the Fall&lt;/a> by Nathan Filer | I got through this book really quickly. I really enjoyed it and found it thought provoking and quite dark, but also funny.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;m currently reading &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/I-Am-Pilgrim-Terry-Hayes/dp/0552160962/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>I Am Pilgrim by Terry Hayes&lt;/a>, and then next up is &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Unlikely-Pilgrimage-Harold-Fry/dp/0552778095/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>The Unlikely Pilgrimage of Harold Fry&lt;/a>. For a bit of non-fiction, Jon &amp;amp; I have both just started reading &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/The-4-Hour-Work-Week-Anywhere/dp/0091929113/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>The 4-Hour Work Week&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>A Chilled Out Weekend</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/a-chilled-out-weekend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2012 18:07:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/a-chilled-out-weekend/</guid><description>&lt;p>Firstly I just want to say Happy mother&amp;rsquo;s day, in particular to my Mum! Hope you&amp;rsquo;ve all had a lovely day :)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>This weekend I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed spending time doing no uni work at all :). Last week I had a test and 2 projects due in so I was working all day and night for all of that, so I decided this weekend would be a chilled out one! Friday night involved watching 3 hours of &lt;a href="http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0108941/" target="_blank">The Stand&lt;/a>, Saturday was a crafty day and today was a beautiful sunny day so I went to town with my boyfriend for a wander and used my birthday vouchers to get a few goodies!&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Scrapbooking&lt;/strong>. On Saturday I continued on my scrapbook which is starting to get a lot bigger. I&amp;rsquo;m scrapping my trip to the US that me and my boyfriend took last summer, gives me holiday blues so much. I will blog about my scrapbook more when it&amp;rsquo;s finished. It&amp;rsquo;s my first attempt at making a scrapbook so it&amp;rsquo;s nothing compared to some people&amp;rsquo;s, but I love this way of keeping my memories!  I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to get the pages together first and then do the journaling after, so some pages are quite plain at the mo. Here&amp;rsquo;s a sneak peak!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/03/IMGP2582.jpg">&lt;img class="size-medium wp-image-400 aligncenter" title="Scrapbook Grand Canyon" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/03/IMGP2582-300x223.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="223" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: center;">&lt;a href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/03/IMGP2584.jpg">&lt;img class="size-medium wp-image-399 aligncenter" title="Scrapbook Monument Valley" src="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/images/2012/03/IMGP2584-300x225.jpg" alt="" width="300" height="225" />&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p style="text-align: left;">2. &lt;strong>Shopping&lt;/strong>. Today I used up most of my birthday vouchers and had a walk around Edinburgh in the sunshine. I managed to pick up the following, and I'm so excited by it all!&lt;/p>
[gallery link="file" order="DESC" orderby="post_date" exclude="400, 399"]
&lt;p>Look how cute those &lt;a href="http://www.paperchase.co.uk/pens-+amp-pencils/panda-highlighters-pack-of-5/invt/00485861/">panda highlighters&lt;/a> are?! I love Paperchase stationery, just wish it was a bit better for the budget. I got that 17 &lt;a href="http://www.boots.com/en/17-Fast-Finish-Nail-Polish_927316/" target="_blank">nail polish&lt;/a> from Boots in &amp;lsquo;Pink Lemonade&amp;rsquo;, will try it out tonight - looks lovely and fresh like summer! Went to The Works too and picked up a canvas for £2.99 - bargain!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I then popped into Waterstones to use my book vouchers. I had looked online for some ideas before I went as I know I&amp;rsquo;d be in there for ages trying to decide between them all! Firstly I bought &lt;a href="http://www.sjwatson-books.com/beforeigotosleep/about/" target="_blank">Before I Go to Sleep&lt;/a> by S. J. Watson - &amp;ldquo;&lt;em>Memories define us. So what if you lost yours every time you went to sleep?&lt;/em> An original, haunting, and deeply chilling debut.&amp;rdquo; I enjoy reading books like this and this one sounds particularly interesting, the boyfriend fancies having a read of this after me too. Then I bought &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Me-Before-You-Jojo-Moyes/dp/0718157834" target="_blank">Me Before You&lt;/a> by Jojo Moyes - a girly book, don&amp;rsquo;t think the boyfriend will read this one :p. I wanted to also buy &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Pink-Hotel-Anna-Stothard/dp/1846881315" target="_blank">The Pink Hotel&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="http://www.amazon.co.uk/Into-Darkest-Corner-Elizabeth-Haynes/dp/0956251579/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;amp;ie=UTF8&amp;amp;qid=1332094500&amp;amp;sr=1-1" target="_blank">Into the Darkest Corner&lt;/a>, but they&amp;rsquo;ll have to wait!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>What have you been up to this weekend? Enjoying the sun where you are?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>