<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>film on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/film/</link><description>Recent content in film on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 21:14:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/film/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Man on a Ledge</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/man-on-a-ledge/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 21:14:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/man-on-a-ledge/</guid><description>&lt;p>Back home now from seeing the second free movie in a row - Man on a Ledge! Well&amp;hellip; I thought it was going to be an alright movie, more my boyfriends type of film, and came away thinking it was just OK. I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t exactly recommend it but it&amp;rsquo;s the type of film that I might put on if it was on TV. It was just a bit cheesy and unrealistic in parts. Just not my cup of tea!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Again Virgin provided us with popcorn, woo! But this time it was in Odeon and their popcorn isn&amp;rsquo;t so nice compared to Cineworld - but I&amp;rsquo;m not gonna complain about free stuff, we still ate it!! We even had our photo taken on the way in :/ We were told it wasn&amp;rsquo;t going on the website it&amp;rsquo;s just to show that they are doing their jobs, phew&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Young Adult</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/young-adult/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2012 22:11:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/young-adult/</guid><description>&lt;p>Just got back from seeing Young Adult at the cinema! Here&amp;rsquo;s a brief bit from IMDb about the storyline of the movie:&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>"Soon after her divorce, a fiction writer returns to her home in small-town Minnesota, looking to rekindle a romance with her ex-boyfriend, who is now happily married and has a newborn daughter."&lt;/blockquote>
I thought it was really good, there's funny bits but it is quite a depressing movie, don't expect a happy ending type! The acting was really good, particularly Charlize Theron (who was actually nominated for a Golden Globe for this film) and Patton Oswalt.
&lt;p>It was pretty busy, but still quite a few spaces left, it&amp;rsquo;s a shame that people miss out when people get the tickets but don&amp;rsquo;t turn up! Looking forward to seeing Man On a Ledge tomorrow thanks to Virgin Media (hopefully we&amp;rsquo;ll get free popcorn as they usually supply us with some!)&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S.&lt;/p>
&lt;p> &lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>