<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>wedding on YayFryDay</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/wedding/</link><description>Recent content in wedding on YayFryDay</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 09:03:25 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://yayfrydayy.com/categories/wedding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Our Wedding Album</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/our-wedding-album/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2017 09:03:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/our-wedding-album/</guid><description>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2018/03/DSC09871.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Our Wedding Album" />&lt;p>After almost a year since our wedding day we finally got around to getting a wedding album. We wanted to get something special and chose to go with the layflat album from &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.artifactuprising.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Artifact Uprising&lt;/a>. It was pricey but the quality is excellent, and we bought it together for our one year &amp;lsquo;paper&amp;rsquo; anniversary.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We picked out our most favourite photos of them all and chose at most one photo per page (with some photos filling a two page spread). I am so pleased with how it came out.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2017/04/DSC09880.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Artifact Uprising Layflat Wedding Album"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2017/04/DSC09885.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Artifact Uprising Layflat Wedding Album"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2017/04/DSC09867.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Artifact Uprising Layflat Wedding Album"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2017/04/DSC09881.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Artifact Uprising Layflat Wedding Album"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2017/04/DSC09886.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Artifact Uprising Layflat Wedding Album"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve just ordered another album that I&amp;rsquo;m currently waiting on, a small soft cover album of our honeymoon. Next step is to get at least one framed print from our wedding in our home. Hopefully it won&amp;rsquo;t take me another year to do.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Honeymoon in the Maldives</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/honeymoon-in-the-maldives/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Apr 2016 18:18:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/honeymoon-in-the-maldives/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6228.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Honeymoon"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Maldives was exactly what we wanted for our honeymoon. Full relaxation on a beautiful tropical island, with blue skies and the clear Indian Ocean. It was even better than I imagined it would be.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We flew from Glasgow to Male with Emirates, with a short stopover in Dubai. We watched a lot of movies during the flights and the food was pretty good - especially the afternoon tea with scones on our flight home. We booked our honeymoon a &lt;a class="link" href="http://yayfryday.com/2015/10/30/wedding-progress/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>few months back&lt;/a> with &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.purelymaldives.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Purely Maldives&lt;/a>, who were fantastic the whole way through and offered us the best deal on flights and accommodation.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Our first two nights were spent in a deluxe beach villa at the all-inclusive &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.oblu-helengeli.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Oblu by Atmosphere at Helengeli&lt;/a>. It was just a short speedboat ride away from Male which was lovely and refreshing. The island was beautiful, with the added bonus of a house reef so we could snorkel from the shore. It&amp;rsquo;s quite a small island which was nice, and all of the staff were excellent. We ate nutella waffles whilst watching the fishes and rays in the sea, snorkelled alongside a blacktip reef shark, drank cocktails, played outdoor table tennis, ate wedding cake, and said &amp;rsquo;this is incredible&amp;rsquo; a lot.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6229.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Oblu Maldives Villa"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6299.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Oblu Maldives Trees"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-1-1.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Oblu Maldives Jetty and Food"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6233.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Oblu Maldives Table Tennis"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6354.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Oblu Maldives Beach Heron"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After Oblu we moved to &lt;a class="link" href="https://atmosphere-kanifushi.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Atmosphere Kanifushi&lt;/a> for five nights. The island is only accessible by seaplane and it was a great experience (though very hot!) and made the greeting on the island even more special. Champagne was waiting for us at reception and in our sunset beach villa. The island felt very luxurious, and it was quite different to Oblu as it was a fair bit bigger, though it still felt very quiet and secluded. The all inclusive here was fantastic, with a mini bar filled twice a day with food and drinks and a choice of places to eat and activities. The outdoor whirlpool bathtub was perfect to relax in and it was lovely to have a private bit of beach tucked away in front of the villa. We watched the sunset in the sea or on the beach each night, ate lobster, went on a sunset cruise, visited a nearby island dedicated to coral research, had a couples massage, snorkelled with fish including lionfish and unicornfishes, drank mojitos, went sea kayaking, and couldn&amp;rsquo;t get over how beautiful these islands are.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-2-1.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Seaplane Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-3-1.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6452.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6610.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6618.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-4.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6719.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6748.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-6.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-8.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6904.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_7138.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-7.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_7188.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-5.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_20160330_181659.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Kanifushi Maldives"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The Maldives, you were paradise.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>25.03.16</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/25-03-16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Apr 2016 20:11:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/25-03-16/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/12885701_1293655207318233_1175845172274274713_o.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Wedding photo"
>
&lt;em>Photo credit: Neil Thomas Douglas&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hoorah we are married! It was a dream come true to marry Jon surrounded by our family and friends, and we both had such a fun day - it really was the best day ever for us. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share some of the details here and a big thank you to everyone for being a part of our special day.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Some photos of our wedding progress leading up to the day (will share some wedding photos soon)..&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-3.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding progress"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6006.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding diy"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_6013.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="origami crane wedding table names"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-1.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="welshcake favours"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/Artboard-2.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="polaroid guest book"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Venue
I wrote &lt;a class="link" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2015/10/30/wedding-progress/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a> about choosing our wedding venue, &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.houseforanartlover.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>House for an Art Lover&lt;/a>. It was perfect for our relaxed wedding, and the team (in particular Robert) were excellent and made sure the day ran smoothly.
We stayed nearby to the venue the night before - Jon with his groomsmen &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.airbnb.co.uk/rooms/7834217" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a> and I stayed with my bridesmaids &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.airbnb.co.uk/rooms/3345932" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>. We all went for dinner the night before which was nice for everyone to meet properly before the wedding. Both houses were Airbnbs and were excellent, and great for getting ready in the morning.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Bride
I chose &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.maggiesottero.com/maggie-sottero/farah/8230" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>my dress&lt;/a> last summer, which I wrote about previously &lt;a class="link" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2015/10/30/wedding-progress/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>. I found and tried on the dress in Cardiff (it was on display in the bridal shop window), but I bought it from &lt;a class="link" href="http://emma-roy.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Emma Roy&lt;/a> up here in Edinburgh. I wanted a dress that was quite simple (not big!) and light, and I loved the detailing to the the top and back. My fittings weren&amp;rsquo;t until the month of the wedding, but luckily it didn&amp;rsquo;t need any alterations except the hem and I had a bustle added in so the train could be lifted for dancing.
I skipped a veil and jewellery since the dress had enough detail with sparkles and pearls, and I wore &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.rainbowclub.co.uk/harlow-peep-toe-satin-shoe" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Rainbow Club&lt;/a> peep toe shoes that I picked up in John Lewis. My hair and make up was done by Lyn Mckenzie and it was exactly what I was looking for - simple and fresh with a pink smokey eye. Lyn also did two bridesmaids and my mum&amp;rsquo;s hair.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Groom
Jon wore a suit from &lt;a class="link" href="http://eu.suitsupply.com/en_GB/suits/lazio-blue-plain/P4123.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Suitsupply&lt;/a>. He ordered a couple of different ones online and decided on the navy Lazio which fit great and he looked fantastic on the day. He wore &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.dunelondon.com/boycy-punch-hole-and-toe-cap-detail-leather-shoe-0272507490002511/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>tan shoes&lt;/a> from Dune, a &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.tmlewin.co.uk/Brown-Contemporary-Belt/40966,en_GB,pd.html?cgid=Mens-Belts-braces&amp;amp;start=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>leather belt&lt;/a> from T.M.Lewin, and a &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.asos.com//Asos/Asos-Slim-Tie-In-Pink-Marl-Effect/Prod/pgeproduct.aspx?iid=5983749" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>blush pink tie&lt;/a>, &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.asos.com//ASOS/ASOS-Silk-Pocket-Square-In-White/Prod/pgeproduct.aspx?iid=5303730" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>white pocket square&lt;/a> and &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.asos.com//Asos/Asos-Tie-Bar-In-Slim-Fit/Prod/pgeproduct.aspx?iid=4315199" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>slim tie bar&lt;/a> from ASOS. Oh and also some &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.tmlewin.co.uk/Navy-Pink-Large-Spot-Socks/55573,en_GB,pd.html?cgid=Mens-Socks-boxers&amp;amp;start=0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>navy and pink polka dot socks&lt;/a> to finish it all off!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Decor
Since the venue was so beautifully decorated with lots of detail already we didn&amp;rsquo;t need to do much in terms of decor. The colours we were going with were grey, navy and blush/peaches. So &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.littlebotanica.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>the flowers&lt;/a> were made up of peach and blush roses with small white tete-a-tete daffodils (Jon &amp;amp; I are both welsh and wanted to incorporate some welsh things - also they smelt amazing), the groomsmen were in navy suits and the bridesmaids in grey dresses. For the tables we had white roses in fishbowls (provided by the venue) and on the long top table we had small vases of white daffodils.
All of the DIY bits were made the week before the wedding. I made the table names using &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.ikea.com/gb/en/catalog/products/30151035/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>IKEA Tolsby frames&lt;/a> by hanging handmade origami cranes in grey, pink and cream along with the table numbers at the bottom. We framed an &amp;lsquo;order of the day&amp;rsquo; and made an instagram hashtag (&lt;a class="link" href="https://www.instagram.com/explore/tags/yayfryday/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>#yayfryday&lt;/a>) sign in photoshop by adapting our &lt;a class="link" href="http://sweetaspi.co.uk/2016/02/26/wedding-invites-diy/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>wedding invite&lt;/a> design.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Guest Book
We had a polaroid guest book, where we used a &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.paperchase.co.uk/gifts/home-and-kitchen-gifts/photo-albums-scrapbooks/kraft-medium-slip-in-album-4x6.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Paperchase photo album&lt;/a> for guests to slip in a polaroid taken on the Fujifilm Instax 210 (borrowed from my work) and write a note on some kraft cards we had set up with sharpies. We also put some &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.gingerray.co.uk/bh-721-photo-booth-props-boho.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Ginger Ray photobooth props&lt;/a> around the guestbook and another IKEA frame with instructions on what to do. We weren&amp;rsquo;t sure how well the guest book would go down as we read that often people need encouraging to use them - but people were queueing up to add to it which was great! We now have a book full of photos and messages that we can look back on.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Food &amp;amp; Drink
The venue included a three course reception meal followed by coffee and tablet, and the food was excellent. We also had lots of wine, fizzy wine and soft drinks as part of our drinks reception and with the speeches/meal. In the evening we had a buffet but most of us were still pretty stuffed from the meal to eat much!
Our &lt;a class="link" href="http://mimisbakehouse.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>cake&lt;/a> was made up of three flavours - red velvet on the bottom, then oreo, and victoria sponge on top - and decorated with buttercream roses on top. The three cakes were bought separately and we purchased a &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.windsorcakecraft.co.uk/windsor_three_tier_spiral_stand.html?category_id=275" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>three tier cake stand&lt;/a> to place them on and added a Ginger Ray &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.gingerray.co.uk/pp-621-cake-bunting-pastel-perfection.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>cake topper&lt;/a>. The cakes were delicious and we saved some money doing it this way.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Photographer
We chose &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.neilthomasdouglas.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Neil&lt;/a> after bookmarking his website a while back. We loved his informal, relaxed and candid style of photography. He was fantastic on the day and we had a lot of comments from people that they thought he was great. We can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see all of the photos - we&amp;rsquo;ve seen a few sneak peeks already and they look fab (the photo at the top of this post is one)!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######The Dancing
In the evening we had a &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.ceilidhminogue.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>ceilidh&lt;/a>. It was so much fun, especially since almost all of our guests hadn&amp;rsquo;t been to one before (including myself), and after the first song the band realised we were definite beginners as it was carnage with everyone going in different directions. After that first song they kept things simple but also challenging enough for us, especially as it got later on in to the night! It kept everyone entertained and we were so glad we chose to have a ceilidh. The band did some DJing as well where they took requests which somehow ended up with the majority of the room doing the macarena at one point&amp;hellip;&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/04/IMG_5759.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="J&amp;S Ampersand"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>######&lt;em>Links&lt;/em>
Brides Gown &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.maggiesottero.com/maggie-sottero/farah/8230" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Farah by Maggie Sottero&lt;/a>
Grooms Suit &lt;a class="link" href="http://eu.suitsupply.com/en_GB/suits/lazio-blue-plain/P4123.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Lazio by Suitsupply&lt;/a>
Wedding Venue &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.houseforanartlover.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>House for an Art Lover&lt;/a>
Shoes &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.rainbowclub.co.uk/harlow-peep-toe-satin-shoe" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Harlow by Rainbow Club&lt;/a>
Florist &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.littlebotanica.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Little Botanica&lt;/a>
Cake &lt;a class="link" href="http://mimisbakehouse.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Mimi’s Bakehouse&lt;/a>
Bridesmaid Dresses &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.coast-stores.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Lori Lee by Coast&lt;/a>
Groomsmen Suits &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.asos.com//ASOS/ASOS-Slim-Suit-Jacket-with-Stretch-in-Navy/Prod/pgeproduct.aspx?iid=5306759" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>ASOS&lt;/a>
Ceilidh Band &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.ceilidhminogue.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Ceilidh Minogue&lt;/a>
Photographer &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.neilthomasdouglas.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Neil Thomas Douglas&lt;/a>
Hair and make up &lt;a class="link" href="http://lynmckenziemakeup.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Lyn Mckenzie&lt;/a>
Nails &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.essie.co.uk/colours/pinks/fiji.aspx" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Fiji by Essie&lt;/a>
Favours &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.fabulouswelshcakes.co.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Fabulous Welshcakes&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Wedding Invites</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/wedding-invites-diy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 23:09:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/wedding-invites-diy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0169.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Hooray - our wedding invites should have arrived with everyone by now. I wanted them to be quite simple, and I am pleased with how they came out.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We started by looking online, places like Etsy, and struggled to find anything we loved. Whilst browsing I stumbled on a link to Creative Market and a downloadable photoshop template which looked just what we were looking for (&lt;a class="link" href="https://creativemarket.com/HitchPaperCo/139680-Wedding-Invitation-Template-Suite" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>). We had them printed with &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.vistaprint.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>Vistaprint&lt;/a> on 5x7 premium matte card stock, and went with the free envelopes.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0142.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 1"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The info and RSVP cards are just 5x7 cards cut in half. All the cards have a grey back, and the invite has an ampersand in Abril Fatface font (which I bookmarked a while back as it looks like a J and S). I made a band with kraft paper to hold together the 3 cards and jazzed up the envelopes a bit with washi tape (purchased &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.thefoxandstar.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>here&lt;/a>).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0135.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 2"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0150.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 3"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0161.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 4"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0155.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 5"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2016/01/DSC_0173.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="wedding invites 6"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>4 weeks to go!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Wedding Progress</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/wedding-progress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2015 15:17:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/wedding-progress/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2015/10/IMG_4401.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="Threipmuir Reservoir"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Wedding plans are coming along nicely (and slowly), so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write a bit here on where I&amp;rsquo;m at currently. We have the venue, the dress, the website and the honeymoon sorted. We also chose our wedding party and picked a colour scheme (navy, peach/blush and grey - the venue has lots of purples too). I won&amp;rsquo;t mention what we still have to do as the list is frighteningly long (I&amp;rsquo;m using Trello to keep me organised), but we have most of the big things sorted so there is less of an urgency for the other bits!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Venue: &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.houseforanartlover.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>House for an Art Lover, Glasgow&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2015/10/hfal.JPG"
loading="lazy"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before anything else we concentrated on the venue. We looked in Scotland and Wales, and in the end decided on House for an Art Lover. The house is beautifully decorated, there are surrounding gardens, there&amp;rsquo;s a different room for each part of the wedding (ceremony, reception and evening), and it came in under our budget. We have visited the house a few times now and each time we discover something new, there are so many little details.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Dress: Undisclosed (sorry!)&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2015/10/IMG_3831-1.JPG"
loading="lazy"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Finding the dress was a relief, and it was fun to try on different types of dresses. I looked in Edinburgh and Cardiff, with the help of my mum, sister and friend. I was stuck between 2/3 and chose the one that stayed in my mind the most. It will be delivered to the store in January and I&amp;rsquo;m excited to try it on in my size! The dress above was one the assistant really wanted me to try on - not the one I chose - don&amp;rsquo;t worry I&amp;rsquo;m not giving anything away :P.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Website: &lt;a class="link" href="http://www.frywedding.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>frywedding.com&lt;/a>&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2015/10/website.png"
loading="lazy"
alt="website screenshot"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We put together a website that holds some key information which we&amp;rsquo;ll also add the RSVP on to once the invites are sent out. It was fun to put together, and we thought it would be a nice way to introduce our wedding party etc.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Honeymoon: The Maldives&lt;/strong>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2015/10/Beach-OBLU-by-Atmosphere-Helengeli-Maldives.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Helengeli Maldives"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At first we found it tough as there were so many options, so one day we went out for lunch and to a coffee shop armed with travel magazines and the macbook. Five days later we booked our honeymoon! At the moment I&amp;rsquo;ve been addicted to watching youtube videos of snorkelling/scuba diving around the island. We are going all inclusive and staying in a beach villa - it looks incredible!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Just under 5 months to go..!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>We're Engaged!</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/tgtrgta/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 21:32:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/tgtrgta/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0892.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>For our 9 year anniversary Jon took us away up North to Perthshire. It was a surprise trip, that somehow he managed to keep secret. We stayed at a beautiful cabin for 2 nights.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0826.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years1"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0759-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years2"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0752.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years3"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0790-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years4"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0727.JPG"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years5"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I still can&amp;rsquo;t get over this place. We drank champagne in the hot tub under the stars, ate great steaks, relaxed in the sauna, sat by the fire, and watched deer in the fields whilst in the double roll top bath.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Jon proposed on Saturday morning when the sun was still rising. I was in my pyjamas and wondered why he was wearing a shirt. Though we both knew it would happen soon I was still surprised when it actually happened. We could not stop smiling and spent the rest of the day dancing around. It was better than I could ever have imagined and I am so excited to marry my best friend and become Mrs Fry.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0813-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years6"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0814-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years7"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0824-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years8"
>
&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0831-copy.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="9years9"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Time to start planning our wedding.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>On Saturday...</title><link>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/on-saturday/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2014 17:41:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://yayfrydayy.com/post/on-saturday/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="http://yayfrydayy.com/images/2014/Dec/DSC_0862-copy-2.jpg"
loading="lazy"
alt="Engaged"
>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>On our 9 year anniversary Jon asked if I would be with him forever, I said &lt;em>yes&lt;/em>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>S. xo&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>